[{"value": {"id": 1830614, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73832", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has issued guidance to special advisers on undertaking opposition research involving individual politicians.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 4820, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "answerText": "As has been the case under successive governments, special advisers are required to adhere to the Code of Conduct for Special Advisers at all times. No specific guidance has been issued on special advisers undertaking opposition research involving individ...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Advisers: Political Parties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830614", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830533, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73751", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his Department\u2019s definition of a working person is for the purposes of policy development in the context of civil service internship schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": ["70510", "71136", "73241"], "answerIsHolding": false, "answerIsCorrection": false, "answeringMemberId": 5305, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "answerText": "The refocused Fast Stream Summer Internship scheme will give talented undergraduates from lower socio-economic backgrounds the opportunity to see what a career in the Civil Service is like. We will assess eligibility for the summer internship scheme based...", "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Service: Unpaid Work", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": [{"questionUin": "70510", "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "71136", "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00"}, {"questionUin": "73241", "dateTabled": "2025-08-29T00:00:00"}]}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830533", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832084, "askingMemberId": 39, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74940", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, in what way he plans to appoint the Chairs of the technical sub-groups on (a) AI and (b) copyright; and what criteria will be used to ensure their impartiality.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832084", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832083, "askingMemberId": 39, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74939", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if he will publish the (a) membership, (b) minutes and (c) Terms of Reference of the (i) working groups on AI and copyright and (ii) technical sub-groups.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832083", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832082, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74938", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to ensure adequate availability of mental health support services for (a) children and (b) young adults.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832082", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832081, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74937", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of the availability of mental health support within schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832081", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832080, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74936", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent mental health support her Department has provided within schools for pupils in Slough.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832080", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832079, "askingMemberId": 4511, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74935", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has had recent discussions with the Iranian authorities on attacks on the Baha\u2019i community including the illegal obtention of property and assets; and what steps i", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832079", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832078, "askingMemberId": 4493, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-10T00:00:00", "uin": "74934", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2025 to Question 61511 on F-35 Aircraft: Israel, whether his Department holds a list of military exports transiting the UK that do not require a licence; and whether t", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832078", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832077, "askingMemberId": 4493, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-10T00:00:00", "uin": "74933", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2025 to Question 61511 on F-35 Aircraft: Israel, what information his Department holds on the re-export of UK-made F-35 components from Israeli suppliers to the global", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832077", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832076, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74932", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he last met with the Patient Safety Commissioner.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832076", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832075, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74931", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of trends in levels of funding allocated to National Trails since 2018 on those trails.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832075", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832074, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74930", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made on increasing the recruitment and training of midwives since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832074", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832073, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74929", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase the recruitment and training of midwives.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832073", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832072, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74928", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he expects the rapid national investigation into NHS maternity and neonatal services to make its initial set of recommendations.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832072", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832071, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74927", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he expects the rapid national investigation into NHS maternity and neonatal services to complete.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832071", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832070, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74926", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to consult (a) the Maternity Safety Alliance and (b) other bereaved families\u2019 groups as part of the national maternity review.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832070", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832069, "askingMemberId": 4513, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74925", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on what date his Department will publish the terms of reference for the national maternity review.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832069", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832068, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74924", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he has made an assessment of the adequacy of the diversions on the Thames path due to the closure of (a) Marsh Lock bridge and (b) Temple Footbridge.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832068", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832067, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74923", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to improve the condition of (a) the Thames path, (b) The Ridgeway and (c) other National Trails.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832067", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832066, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74922", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2025 to Question 25560 on National Trails UK: Finance, what his timetable is for announcing the funding settlement for (a) National Trails UK, (b) ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832066", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832065, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74921", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason outstanding pension payments to veterans under the McCloud Pension Remedy are being delayed.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832065", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832064, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74920", "questionText": "To ask the hon. Member for Blaenau Gwent and Rhymney, representing the House of Commons Commission, what is the annual cost of the Belu water used in the House of Commons; and when the contract was last tendered.", "answeringBodyId": 18, "answeringBodyName": "House of Commons Commission", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832064", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832063, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74919", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will make it his policy to stop UK (a) owned and (b) insured LNG carriers from transporting Russian products.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832063", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832062, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74918", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to support (a) local authorities and (b) police forces to manage tensions around asylum seeker housing.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832062", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832061, "askingMemberId": 5149, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74917", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to improve public awareness of drinking water (a) safety and (b) quality standards.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832061", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832060, "askingMemberId": 5149, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74916", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of per- and polyfluoroalkyl substance contamination in drinking water in England.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832060", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832059, "askingMemberId": 5149, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74915", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department plans to support national expansion of the Yellowfish campaign to reduce drain contamination.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832059", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832058, "askingMemberId": 5076, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74914", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the availability of residential training places for disabled young people in Scotland on proposed changes to eligibility for Universal Credit for ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832058", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832057, "askingMemberId": 5149, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74913", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure clear consumer labelling on wet wipes marketed as flushable.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832057", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832056, "askingMemberId": 5149, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74912", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his planned timetable is for banning wet wipes containing plastic.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832056", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832055, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74911", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of climate-related wildfires on fire service budgets;\u00a0and what steps she is taking to ensure sustainable fun", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832055", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832054, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74910", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department plans to consult (a) fire authorities, (b) local councils and (c) the insurance sector on potential alternative funding mechanisms for fire services.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832054", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832053, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74909", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department has made\u00a0an estimate\u00a0of the potential annual revenue that could be generated by a \u00a31 to \u00a32 levy on all (a) home and (b) vehicle insurance policies for prov", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832053", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832052, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74908", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department\u00a0has had discussions with the insurance industry on the potential feasibility of a per-policy contribution to fire service funding.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832052", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832051, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74907", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department has considered introducing a statutory levy on (a) home and (b) vehicle insurance policies to provide direct funding to fire and rescue services.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832051", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832050, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74906", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether his Department is taking steps to support retail workers who report abuse while working alone.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832050", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832049, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74905", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he has considered commissioning a review into the (a) prevalence and (b) potential risks of lone working in the retail sector.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832049", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832048, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74904", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will have discussions with the Co-operative Group on Project Lunar.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832048", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832047, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74903", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will make an assessment of\u00a0the adequacy of existing guidance issued to retailers on lone working.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832047", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832046, "askingMemberId": 4475, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74902", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department\u00a0taking to ensure that retail employers comply with health and safety regulations in relation to lone working.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832046", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832045, "askingMemberId": 4511, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74901", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether HS2 plans to revisit the allocation of strategic funding to the London Borough of Ealing.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832045", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832044, "askingMemberId": 4869, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74900", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure adequate mental health support is provided to Physician Associates following the publication of the Leng Review.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832044", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832043, "askingMemberId": 4493, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74899", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2025 to Question 56288 on Arms Trade: Israel, if he will now publish the Research Report: Long-Range Shootings or Shootings of Minors that was included in evidence in A", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832043", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832042, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74898", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 2 April 2025 to Question 41875, when she plans to respond to correspondence from the hon. Member for Arbroath and Broughty Ferry of 31 January 202", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832042", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832041, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74897", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June to Question 61525 on RAF Brize Norton: Security, when he plans to publish the security review into the defence estate.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832041", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832040, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74896", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time is for a first appointment with a consultant in NHS trusts in Lancashire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832040", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832039, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74895", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's White Paper entitled Restoring Control over the Immigration System, published on 12 May 2025, when she plans to publish further information on the expansion to the p", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832039", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832038, "askingMemberId": 4084, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74894", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2025 to Question 34608 on Vaccine Damage Payment Scheme: Appeals, whether past tribunal decisions are used to support assessments.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832038", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832037, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74893", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of Darwin Plus on maintaining the British Overseas Territories' environmental heritage.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832037", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832036, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74892", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of reinstating Darwin Plus.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832036", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832035, "askingMemberId": 5277, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74891", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of abolishing peak fares for rail passengers.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832035", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832034, "askingMemberId": 5302, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-10T00:00:00", "uin": "74890", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure transparency in the allocation of licences for commercial bluefin tuna fishery; and if he will make an assessment of the potential merits ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832034", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832033, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74889", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of extending pensions automatic enrolment to jobholders under the age of 22 on those people.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832033", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832032, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74888", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she plans to implement the Pensions (Extension of Automatic Enrolment) Act 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832032", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832031, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74887", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what estimate his Department has made of the number of employees who work alone in retail environments; and what steps his Department is taking to monitor trends in lone working practices.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832031", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832030, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74886", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment her Department has made of the potential health and safety risks associated with increased lone working in retail.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832030", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832029, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74885", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that women in the armed forces are equipped with appropriate (a) uniforms and (b) equipment.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832029", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832028, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74884", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the Pensions (Extension of Automatic Enrolment) Act 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832028", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832027, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74883", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2025 to Question 63017 on Housing Estates: Unadopted Roads, whether the public will be able to contribute to the consultation into new consumer p", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832027", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832026, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74882", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2025 to Question 63017 on Housing Estates: Unadopted Roads, when her Department plans to launch a consultation on new consumer protection provisi", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832026", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832025, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74881", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department plans to enable freeholding residents to seek binding changes to deeds when management falls below reasonable standards.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832025", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832024, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74880", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department plans to require estate management companies to publish detailed financial records.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832024", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832023, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74879", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department plans to allow freeholding residents to (a) challenge and (b) replace estate management companies.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832023", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832022, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74878", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish guidance to Hon. Members on how students in Gaza who are eligible for support to come to the UK can access this support; and if she will provide a dedicated communication pathway f", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832022", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832021, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74877", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take further steps to support children's hospices with their energy costs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832021", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832020, "askingMemberId": 5133, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74876", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the (a) supply and (b) availability of mefenamic acid for people in (i) the East of England and (ii) England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832020", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832019, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74875", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of harmonising gambling tax rates on the horseracing industry.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832019", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832018, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74874", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many seats were booked on deportation charter flights in the last year; and how many were used.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832018", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832017, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74873", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many charter flights for deportations were scheduled in the last 12 months; and how many took place.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832017", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832016, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74872", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of foreign nationals who have abscond after being served with a deportation order.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832016", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832015, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74871", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of staff in her Department are dedicated to enforcing deportation orders.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832015", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832014, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74870", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the backlog in deportation cases.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832014", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832013, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74869", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of foreign nationals living in the UK unlawfully who are liable for deportation.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832013", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832012, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74868", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many deportations have been delayed as a result of injunctions granted by domestic courts citing the European Convention on Human Rights in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832012", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832011, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74867", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many deportations have been delayed as a result of challenges under Article 8 of the European Convention on Human Rights in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832011", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832010, "askingMemberId": 5182, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74866", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has considered introducing multi-year NHS funding for the health elements of children's palliative care.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832010", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832009, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74865", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to legislate to disapply the Human Rights Act 1998 in deportation cases.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832009", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832008, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74864", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many deportations have been prevented by interim measures of the European Court of Human Rights in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832008", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832007, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74863", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of publishing league tables of deportation compliance by countries.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832007", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832006, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74862", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department\u2019s policy is on restricting multiple appeals against deportation.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832006", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832005, "askingMemberId": 4995, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74861", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) export opportunities and (b) support needs for (i) manufacturers and (ii) suppliers of (A) machinery and (B) technology used by the (1) agricultural a", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832005", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832004, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74860", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of legal aid support in deportation cases in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832004", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832003, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74859", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has sought to negotiate returns agreements with (a) Pakistan, (b) Albania, (c) Nigeria and (d) Somalia in the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832003", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832002, "askingMemberId": 4995, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74858", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of (a) introducing targeted support for small and medium-sized enterprises exhibiting at sector-relevant international trade shows and (b) esta", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832002", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832001, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74857", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of deportations that have failed due to a lack of cooperation from foreign governments.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832001", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1832000, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74856", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department applies sanctions to countries that refuse to accept deported nationals.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1832000", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831999, "askingMemberId": 4995, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74855", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the trends in the number of business closures in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831999", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831998, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74854", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the proposed abolition of NHS England on the (a) recruitment and (b) training of NHS staff.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831998", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831997, "askingMemberId": 5160, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74853", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his planned timeline is for introducing legislation to prohibit the import of hunting trophies.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831997", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831996, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74852", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the Financial Conduct Authority\u2019s regulatory framework for insurance companies\u2019 use of loss adjusters; and whether she plans to regulate the conduct of loss adjusters.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831996", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831995, "askingMemberId": 5160, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74851", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to publish draft legislative proposals to ban trail hunting.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831995", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831994, "askingMemberId": 5160, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74850", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what support is available to small businesses affected by changes in Small Business Rate Relief.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831994", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831993, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74849", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the abolition of NHS England on the recruitment and training of NHS staff.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831993", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831992, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74848", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the abolition of NHS England does not affect the delivery of frontline services for patients.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831992", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831991, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74847", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the abolition of NHS England on the structure of his Department.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831991", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831990, "askingMemberId": 4656, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74846", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of introducing an external delivery model to help the teaching of financial education in schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831990", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831989, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74845", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the abolition of NHS England on patient safety.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831989", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831988, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74844", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the impact of the abolition of NHS England on staff morale.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831988", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831987, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74843", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the abolition of NHS England on the NHS Business Services Authority.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831987", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831986, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74842", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the abolition of NHS England on NHS hospital trusts.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831986", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831985, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74841", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the abolition of NHS England on (a) NHS Digital Services and (b) the (i) storage and (ii) retention of patient data.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831985", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831984, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74840", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what Parliamentary process will be followed prior to the implementation of the Equality and Human Rights Commission's Code of Practice for Services, Public Functions, and Associations.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831984", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831983, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74839", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his planned timetable is for bringing forward legislative proposals to abolish NHS England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831983", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831982, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74838", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent progress his Department has made on the abolition of NHS England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831982", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831981, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74837", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish the estimate of the potential savings to the public purse following the abolition of NHS England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831981", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831980, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74836", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to respond to Question 64587 on Defence Growth Board, tabled on 2 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831980", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831979, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74835", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Oral Statement of 1 September 2025 on Ukraine, Official Report, columns 93-94, whether the conclusions of the armed forces readiness levels review will be broken down by service.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831979", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831978, "askingMemberId": 5214, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74834", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to support (a) prison and (b) probation staff.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831978", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831977, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74833", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to confirm the cost of the redundancy package for staff being made redundant from (a) NHS England and (b) his Department.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831977", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831976, "askingMemberId": 4776, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74832", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the cost of noise pollution to the economy.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831976", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831975, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74831", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase access to Givinostat for patients in North Shropshire constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831975", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831974, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74830", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the headcount of staff members was at (a) his Department and (b) NHS England in each month between February and September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831974", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831973, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74829", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps his Department is taking to support Openreach to provide fibre to the premises connections in (a) Alfriston Road, Berwick and (b) other rural areas in Lewes constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831973", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831972, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74828", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her department is taking to reduce the Child Disability Living Allowance claim time.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831972", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831971, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74827", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications (a) by adults and (b) on behalf of children for Disability Living Allowance benefits are outstanding; and what is the average waiting time for these applications to be resolved.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831971", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831970, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74826", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 3 September 2025 to Question 70331 on Northern Ireland Troubles (Legacy and Reconciliation) Act 2023, if he will set out his planned timetable for (a) responding to the Joint Co", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831970", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831969, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74825", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 3 September 2025 to Question 70329 on Terrorism: Northern Ireland, in which jurisdiction is the trial taking place for the individual currently awaiting trial; and which jurisdi", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831969", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831968, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74824", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to help (a) local authorities and (b) Trading Standards take action against rogue builders; and what steps her Department is taking to improve", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831968", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831967, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74823", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department holds information on the number of rogue builders prosecuted in England in each of the past three financial years.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831967", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831966, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74822", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to continue the Sustainable Farming Incentive.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831966", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831965, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74821", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure the future of agri-environmental farming schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831965", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831964, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74820", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the consultation on poultry catching and handling, which ended on 2 May 2025, what steps he is taking to ensure that the research project to study the impact of vario", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831964", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831963, "askingMemberId": 4861, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74819", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help support young farmers.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831963", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831962, "askingMemberId": 4861, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74818", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, to which organisations his Department has allocated discretionary grants for the 2026-27 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831962", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831961, "askingMemberId": 1211, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74817", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help reduce the time taken to provide treatment for people with an eating disorder.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831961", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831960, "askingMemberId": 1211, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74816", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of parents with (a) three and (a) four year old children used their entitlement to 15 hours of free childcare in Sutton Coldfield constituency in 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831960", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831959, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74815", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to review cases of people born in the UK before 1 July 2006 to a British father and a non-British mother where the parents were not married, who sought registration under sectio", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831959", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831958, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74814", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, when his Department plans to respond to the email from the hon. Member for Newton Abbot dated 24 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831958", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831957, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74813", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when she plans to respond to the email from the hon. Member for Newton Abbot dated 24 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831957", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831956, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74812", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to remove asbestos from schools in South Holland and the Deepings constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831956", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831955, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74811", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 6 August to Question 67990 on Hussam Abu Safiya, what recent discussions he has had with (a) the Israeli Deputy Foreign Minister and (b) Israel\u2019s am", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831955", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831954, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74810", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when she plans to respond to the correspondence of 16 July 2025 from the hon. Member for Newton Abbot.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831954", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831953, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74809", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the decision to restrict TechExpert scholarships to domestic PhD students on the UK\u2019s international competitiveness in Artificial ", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831953", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831952, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74808", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of university-based (a) research and (b) development activities on levels of UK (i) productivity and (ii) economic growth.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831952", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831951, "askingMemberId": 5142, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74807", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate she has made of the net financial impact of international students to the economy.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831951", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831950, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74806", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to help tackle fraud in car parks.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831950", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831949, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74805", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to help prevent the (a) sale and (b) production of skimming devices used fraudulently steal card details.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831949", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831948, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74804", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of the consumption of high caffeine energy drinks on (a) schools and (b) educational outcomes.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831948", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831947, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74803", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason the number of cohorts has been reduced in the Future High Potential Initial Teacher Training Programme contract.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831947", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831946, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74802", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason the indicative total contract value for the Future High Potential Initial Teacher Training Programme contract has reduced from \u00a3150 million in April 2025 to \u00a389 million in September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831946", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831945, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74801", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of the consumption of high caffeine energy drinks on health services in Lancashire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831945", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831944, "askingMemberId": 5293, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74800", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the operation of NHS Practitioner Health beyond March 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831944", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831943, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74799", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has considered establishing a framework enabling asylum-seeking students to access (a) internships, (b) placements and (c) other forms of work experience that support their university cour", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831943", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831942, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74798", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking with Cabinet colleagues to ensure climate adaptation plans are in place across all sectors to prevent adverse impacts on (a) women\u2019s health and (b) pregnancy outcomes.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831942", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831941, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74797", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on increasing the women's healthcare workforce to ensure services can meet rising demand and deliver the NHS 10-Year Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831941", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831940, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74796", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of reducing waiting times for gynaecology services on women\u2019s ability to return to or remain in work.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831940", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831939, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74795", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on reducing waiting times for gynaecology services.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831939", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831938, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74794", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking with Cabinet colleagues to ensure that women's health is included in the Government's approach to prevention across the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831938", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831937, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74793", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to ensure that women\u2019s health is included in the Government's plans to reform the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831937", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831936, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74792", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to support the development and expansion of Women\u2019s Health Hubs.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831936", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831935, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74791", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on updating the Women\u2019s Health Strategy in response to the publication of the 10-Year NHS Plan for England.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831935", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831934, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74790", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care\u00a0on tackling racial disparities in maternity care in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831934", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831933, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74789", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking with Cabinet colleagues to improve the quality of maternity care for women across the country.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831933", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831932, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74788", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support (a) local transport authorities and (b) bus operators to increase use of (i) hybrid, (ii) electric and (iii) hydrogen buses on local tran", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831932", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831931, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74787", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, when CityFibre will install fibre to in-scope postcodes in East Hampshire constituency; and whether this has been delayed.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831931", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831930, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74786", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking with the Mayor of London to reduce air pollution levels in (a) Clapham and Brixton Hill constituency and (b) London.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831930", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831929, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74785", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the Department of Health and Social Care on the health impact of air pollution levels in Clapham and Brixton Hill constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831929", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831928, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74784", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has carried out a health-impact assessment on the levels of air pollution in Clapham and Brixton Hill constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831928", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831927, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74783", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of trends in air pollution levels in Clapham and Brixton Hill constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831927", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831926, "askingMemberId": 3969, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74782", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, which postcodes are in scope in the Hampshire CityFibre contract in East Hampshire constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831926", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831925, "askingMemberId": 4995, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74781", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether Gypsy and Traveller sites will be included in the next round of Social and Affordable Homes Programme funding.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831925", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831924, "askingMemberId": 5197, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74780", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he plans to take to increase shipbuilding capacity.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831924", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831923, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74779", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received (a) warnings and (b) punishment for underpaying stamp duty in the last financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831923", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831922, "askingMemberId": 5219, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74778", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that the contracted suppliers for the Disabled Students' Allowance are transparent with students on pricing.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831922", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831921, "askingMemberId": 5066, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74777", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that Police and Crime Commissioners are held accountable to their respective Police and Crime Panels.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831921", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831920, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74776", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to introduce nature-friendly farming schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831920", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831919, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74775", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 22 August 2025 to Question 69070 on Syria: Inter Mediate, for what reason his Department does not disclose details of the individual projects funded", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831919", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831918, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74774", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how many and what proportion of staff in his Department are assigned to work on the China strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831918", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831917, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74773", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2025 to Question 66657 on Civil Service: Resignations, if he will publish the responses from the Permanent Under-Secretaries.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831917", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831916, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74772", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 12 November 2024 to Question HL2064 on Diego Garcia: Military Bases, how many letters were sent between the two governments on the draft treat", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831916", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831915, "askingMemberId": 152, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74771", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what support his Department has offered to British citizens accused of being co-conspirators in the closing days of the trial of Jimmy Lai in Hong Kong; and what assessment h", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831915", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831914, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74770", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2025 to Question 54790 on FCDO: Holidays, whether there is any further internal guidance to Ministers on this issue.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831914", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831913, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74769", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether (a) his Department and (b) the British Council has provided funding to Common Purpose since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831913", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831912, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74768", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether his Department has spent money on (a) digital and (b) social influencers since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831912", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831911, "askingMemberId": 5078, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74767", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will exempt full time students from paying Court of Protection Fees.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831911", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831910, "askingMemberId": 5216, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74766", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 June 2025 to Question 56493 on Teachers' Pensions, what progress she has made on resolving outstanding Cash Equivalent Transfer Value cases.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831910", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831909, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74765", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Written Statement of 21 July 2025 on Government of service, HCWS870, whether the Prime Minister plans to issue a direction under section 17 of the Constitutional Reform and Governance Act 2", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831909", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831908, "askingMemberId": 5294, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74764", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June to Question 57910 on Legal Aid Scheme, how much the Legal Aid Agency paid in fees to Duncan Lewis LLP in (a) 2021-22, (b) 2022-23, (c) 2023-24, and (d) 2024-25 related to immigra", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831908", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831907, "askingMemberId": 5294, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74763", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish a list of the (a) names and (b) locations of former airforce bases within the UK that are no longer in use by the Royal Air Force but remain part of the Ministry of Defence estate as of 1 Septe", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831907", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831906, "askingMemberId": 5265, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74762", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of a scheme to support police officers and emergency call handlers in obtaining (a) housing and (b) mental health support.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831906", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831905, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74761", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, by what means the Weeds Act 1959 is being enforced.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831905", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831904, "askingMemberId": 4818, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74760", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of trends in the level of borrowing costs on mortgages.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831904", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831903, "askingMemberId": 4818, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74759", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has had discussions with Cabinet colleagues on the potential impact of the trends in the cost of debt on Departmental Budgets.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831903", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831902, "askingMemberId": 4818, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74758", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has had discussions with the International Monetary Fund on the impact of the rising cost of bond yields.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831902", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831901, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74757", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when NICE last reviewed its guidance on the (a) availability and (b) prescribing of T3 for the treatment of thyroid cancer; and whether he has plans to improve access to T3 for patients where it is", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831901", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831900, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74756", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, by what date she expects all police forces in England and Wales to have full operational access to the TOEX Capabilities Environment.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831900", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831899, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74755", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of giving National Highways a remit to increase the efficiency of motorways and major A roads by incentivising increasing the number of people in a car.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831899", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831898, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74754", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to expand the provision of high occupancy vehicle lanes in England.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831898", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831897, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74753", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to support the increased use of (a) car-pooling and (b) lift sharing.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831897", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831896, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74752", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of reports of attacks against Christian communities in Sudan; and what diplomatic steps he is takin", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831896", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831895, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74751", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to support the increased use of Car Clubs.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831895", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831894, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74750", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria her Department used to allocate the funding for the national expansion of the TOEX Capabilities Environment.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831894", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831893, "askingMemberId": 5175, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74749", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what progress the Government has made on (a) ensuring equal treatment for BCSSS members and (b) transferring the whole of the investment reserve to the benefit of all members.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831893", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831892, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74748", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the scope of Operation Beaconport is.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831892", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831891, "askingMemberId": 1516, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74747", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make his policy to talk to his Moroccan counterpart on the blocking of visits by (a) parliamentarians, (b) researchers, (c) journalists and (d) lawyers to occupied", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831891", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831890, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74746", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to address geographic variations in (a) access and (b) efficacy of treatment for multiple sclerosis in (i) the South West and (ii) England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831890", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831889, "askingMemberId": 1516, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74745", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make it his policy to call on MINURSO to (a) conduct human rights monitoring in Western Sahara and (b) report their finding to the UN Security Council.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831889", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831888, "askingMemberId": 1516, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74744", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department\u2019s policies of the UN Secretary General\u2019s designation of Western Sahara as a non-self-governing territory in", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831888", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831887, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74743", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which units are using FV433 Bulldog vehicles; and how many each unit has.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831887", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831886, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74742", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of benefit claimants have been subject to sanctions in Lincolnshire in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831886", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831885, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74741", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many FV433 Bulldog vehicles are in service.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831885", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831884, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74740", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many properties have been procured by (a) her Department and (b) contracted companies to serve as dispersal housing for asylum seekers in (i) South Holland and the Deepings constituency and (ii) L", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831884", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831883, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74739", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to procure additional Ares vehicles beyond the 93 ordered.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831883", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831882, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74738", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 29 April 2025 to Question 48996 on Armoured Fighting Vehicles: Decommissioning, what progress he has made on procuring a replacement for the Jackal 2 Reconnaissance Vehicle.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831882", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831881, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74737", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 29 April 2025 to Question 48996 on Armoured Fighting Vehicles: Decommissioning, what progress he has made on procuring a replacement for the Bulldog Armoured Personnel Carrier.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831881", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831880, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74736", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 29 April 2025 to Question 48996 on Armoured Fighting Vehicles: Decommissioning, what progress he has made on procuring replacement for the Viking Personnel Armoured Vehicle.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831880", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831879, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74735", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of cancer patients in Lincolnshire received treatment within 62 days in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831879", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831878, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74734", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the responsibilities are of the National Situation Centre.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831878", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831877, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74733", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 3 September 2025 to Question 70001 on Voting Rights: Cambridgeshire, whether the Impact Assessment to be published alongside forthcoming legislation wil", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831877", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831876, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74732", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Statement on Strengthening border security and reforms to the asylum system of 1 September 2025, whether applicants to the Ukrainian Permission Extension scheme who applied in Sp", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831876", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831875, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74731", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many instances of clinical negligence in which NHS Resolution paid damages there were in each clinical speciality in the (a) 2023-24 and (b) 2024-25 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831875", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831874, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74730", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the total cost to the public purse is for (a) clinical negligence and (b) other claims against the National Health Service in England paid out by NHS Resolution in the (i) 2023-24 and (ii) 202", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831874", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831873, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74729", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which NHS Trusts will be involved in the Rapid National Investigation into maternity and neonatal services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831873", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831872, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74728", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department has issued to local education authorities to support school pupils with (a) endometriosis and (b) other (i) menstrual and (ii) reproductive health concerns.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831872", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831871, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74727", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve GP (a) training in and (b) awareness of (i) endometriosis and (ii) women\u2019s health issues in general.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831871", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831870, "askingMemberId": 5317, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74726", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve access to (a) mental health and (b) pain management support for people with endometriosis.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831870", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831869, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74725", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of Mounjaro (a) prescribing and (b) medication management services his Department plans to carry out digitally.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831869", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831868, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74724", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his Department's publication entitled 10 Year Health Plan for England: fit for the future, published on 3 July 2025, what progress his Department has made on the digital-only deli", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831868", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831867, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74723", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he has had recent discussions with retailers on the safety and security of people who are lone working in stores.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831867", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831866, "askingMemberId": 5141, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74722", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of allowing NHS trusts to reduce mileage reimbursement to incentivise use of pool vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831866", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831865, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-10T00:00:00", "uin": "74721", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to help ensure school bus travel is (a) affordable and (b) accessible in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831865", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831864, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74720", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many applications were submitted for household extensions in (a) 2023-24 and (b) 2024-25.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831864", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831863, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74719", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 4 August 2025 to Question HL9815 on Electoral Register, what her planned timetable is for the commissioning of user research.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831863", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831862, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74718", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to page 81 of her Department's annual report and accounts 2024-25, published in July 2025, HC 1062, for what reason core departmental contingent labour spending in", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831862", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831861, "askingMemberId": 5225, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74717", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he is considering taking steps to standardise fees charged by veterinary practices for issuing animal health certificates.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831861", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831860, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74716", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what representations her Department has received from the Labour Infrastructure Forum.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831860", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831859, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74715", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 1 April 2025 to Question 41927 on Housing: Construction, what proportion of the 1.3 million homes forecast related to England alone.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831859", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831858, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74714", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what guidance her Department has issued on whether the conversion of a residential dwelling into a House in Multiple Occupation for asylum seekers requires (a) planning permissio", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831858", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831857, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74713", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make it her policy to introduce a national find my councillor facility on gov.uk.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831857", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831856, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74712", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she has considered bringing forward legislative proposals on Empty Dwelling Management Orders.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831856", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831855, "askingMemberId": 4716, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74711", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent diplomatic steps his Department has taken in the context of deaths among (a) political and (b) religious prisoners in Nicaragua.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831855", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831854, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74710", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 5 August 2025 to Question HL9813 on Combatting Hate against Muslims Fund, whether she plans to spend the remaining \u00a3350,000 of the fund in the 202", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831854", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831853, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74709", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has spent money on promotion through social media influencers since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831853", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831852, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74708", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has spent money on promotion through social media influencers since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831852", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831851, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74707", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2025 to Question 62596 on Greater Manchester Combined Authority: Property Development, what information (a) her Department and (b) Homes England ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831851", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831850, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74706", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether his Department has spent money on promotion through social media influencers since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831850", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831849, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74705", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has spent money on promotion through social media influencers since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831849", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831848, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74704", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department has spent money on promotion through social media influencers since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831848", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831847, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74703", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he expects to receive the report of the latest review of prostate cancer diagnosis from from the UK National Screening Committee.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831847", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831846, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74702", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 20 June 2025 to Question 60425 on Sustainable Farming Incentive, what his planned timetable is for announcing further details of the reformed Sustainable Farm", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831846", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831845, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74701", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Defence on the use of military sites to house asylum seekers.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831845", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831844, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74700", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which military sites her Department has assessed for housing asylum seekers.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831844", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831843, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74699", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of co-locating (a) inhalers, (b) adrenaline auto injectors and (c) other emergency medical treatment alongside defibrillators in the community se", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831843", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831842, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74698", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of defibrillators have a collocated bleed/trauma pack.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831842", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831841, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74697", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of nurses qualifying this summer have secured nursing jobs in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831841", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831840, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74696", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has made of the potential merits of electronic prescribing in secondary care settings.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831840", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831839, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74695", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential cyber security implications of his policy to make the NHS the most artificial intelligence enabled care system in the world, as set out in the 10 Year", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831839", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831838, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74694", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of extending Eurostar services to Bedford in the context of the Universal UK theme park.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831838", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831837, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74693", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will have discussions with the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government on sourcing black bin waste from councils for use in the production of sustainable aviation fuels.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831837", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831836, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74692", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero on increasing sustainable aviation fuel production in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831836", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831835, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74691", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of business rates on pub closures.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831835", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831834, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74690", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking to ensure that savers have access to high return investment options.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831834", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831833, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74689", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to her Department's press release entitled Government completes exit from NatWest, published on 30 May 2025, if she will publish Departmental analysis of the (a) chosen and (b) retail model of sale.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831833", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831832, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74688", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has conducted an impact assessment for the UK-India trade deal.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831832", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831831, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74687", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what her planned thresholds are for income tax in 2029-30.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831831", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831830, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74686", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has made an assessment of the sectoral economic impact of US tariffs.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831830", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831829, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74685", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of US tariffs on economic growth.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831829", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831828, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74684", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to introduce incentives for British businesses that produce Sustainable Aviation Fuels.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831828", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831827, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74683", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of increasing Sustainable Aviation Fuel production in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831827", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831826, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74682", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of recent trends in the level of business confidence.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831826", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831825, "askingMemberId": 5316, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74681", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department plans to accept the recommendations of the Older People\u2019s Housing Taskforce Report, published on 26 November 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831825", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831824, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-05T00:00:00", "uin": "74680", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential implications for her policies of trends in the (a) number and (b) differing typologies of incidents of transnational repression in the last fiv", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831824", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831823, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74679", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of providing unredacted access to the war records of ancestors of members of Polish forces who fought alongside the British Army in World War Two.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831823", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831822, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-05T00:00:00", "uin": "74678", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Housing Benefit earnings disregard for young people in supported accommodation was last reviewed; and whether her Department plans to reassess its adequacy.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831822", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831821, "askingMemberId": 5273, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74677", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department has had discussions with British Paralympic Association on the selection process for Paralympians.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831821", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831820, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74676", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2025 to Question 63282 on Business: Cybercrime, what steps the National Cyber Security Centre is taking to tackle those incidents of cyber cr", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831820", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831819, "askingMemberId": 5218, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-05T00:00:00", "uin": "74675", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to address regulatory failings highlighted in the independent review by Malcolm Sheehan KC concerning the collapse of football index.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831819", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831818, "askingMemberId": 4608, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74674", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his proposed ban on trophy hunting imports will include the (a) import and (b) export of hunting trophies, (c) enforcement of existing (i) national and (ii) international laws ", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831818", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831817, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74673", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Internship Scheme To Get More Working Class Students Into Civil Service, published on 1 August 2025, whether children of asylum seekers that (a) are perm", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831817", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831816, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74672", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2025 to Question 58020 on Chinese Embassy: Planning Permission and further to the correspondence from the MHCLG Planning Casework Unit to DP9 of ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831816", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831815, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74671", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether he has made an assessment of the potential economic impact of attracting American research scientists in (a) cancer and (b) Alzheimer's on UK research.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831815", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831814, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74670", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps he is taking to provide funding support to support UK research institutions to recruit American scientists from US universities.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831814", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831813, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74669", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of introducing targeted (a) visa and (b) relocation support for American scientists seeking to work in the UK in the fields of ", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831813", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831812, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74668", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the UK has made an assessment of the potential merits of providing unmanned ground vehicles (UGVs) to Ukraine as part of its military support package.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831812", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831811, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74667", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many non-party political life peers he intends to ask the Commission to nominate in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831811", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831810, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74666", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy to ensure that people who are white British are eligible to apply for all (a) government and (b) (i) MI5 and (ii) MI6 summer internships.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831810", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831809, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74665", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on the number of civil servants who are (a) full protection and (b) tapered protection members of the Civil Service (i) Classic, (ii) Premium, (iii) Classic Plus and (iv) Nu", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831809", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831808, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74664", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Written Statement on Government of service, HCWS870, of 21 July 2025, whether the new Business Appointment Rules administered by the Civil Service Commission will apply to (a) special advis", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831808", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831807, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74663", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Written Statement on Government of service, HCWS870, of 21 July 2025, whether he plans to amend the Civil Service Management Code to reflect the transfer of the Advisory Committee on Busine", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831807", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831806, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74662", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Written Statement of 21 July 2025, HCWS870, on Government of service, whether he plans to amend the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 to implement the changes on Minister", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831806", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831805, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74661", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Written Statement of 21 July 2025 on Government of service, HCWS870, whether he plans to permit retrospective applications for business appointments to the (a) Civil Service Commission and ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831805", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831804, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74660", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 21 July 2025 to Question HL9163 on Government Departments: Regulation, how many authorisations have been made within this Department.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831804", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831803, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74659", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his Department's planned timetable is for publishing details of the new arrangements for applications relating to Business Appointments Rules.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831803", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831802, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-05T00:00:00", "uin": "74658", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of applications from (a) ministers to the Advisory Committee on Business Appointments were processed with substantive advice within 15 working days and (b) all other crown servants at SCS3 or equ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831802", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831801, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74657", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 28 July 2025 to Question 57266 on Domestic Visits: Doncaster, which events the special advisers who travelled with the Prime Minister to Doncaster took ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831801", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831800, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74656", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish the terms and conditions for non-executive board member appointments agreed to by Alan Milburn.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831800", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831799, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74655", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she plans to take to help tackle inequalities experienced by young disabled people at work.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831799", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831798, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74654", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve fracture screening.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831798", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831797, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74653", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the childhood cancer survival rate in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831797", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831796, "askingMemberId": 5273, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74652", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans to review the requirement for small businesses to file profits and losses with Companies House.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831796", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831795, "askingMemberId": 5273, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74651", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of (a) unprocessed and (b) minimally processed foods on public health.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831795", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831794, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74650", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to publish a description of the new job role for physician associates before implementation of the Leng Review.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831794", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831793, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74649", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has has local stakeholders in response to Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman\u2019s findings on WASPI women in West Dorset.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831793", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831792, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74648", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment she has made of the potential impact of trends in the level of costs of (a) energy, (b) water and (c) business rates on the viability of pubs in West Dorset constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831792", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831791, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74647", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps her Department is taking to decrease (a) National Insurance and (b) business rates costs for pubs (i) since the Spending Review and (ii) ahead of the Autumn Budget in (A) rural constituencies and (B) West", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831791", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831790, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74646", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department issue updated guidance for rural local authorities as part of the proposed review of Contest.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831790", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831789, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74645", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's announcement entitled Investment for Border Security Command to tackle people smuggling gangs of 3 August 2025, what the responsibilities of the 300 additional Natio", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831789", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831788, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74644", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, by when does he plan to conclude the policy development phase of the Review of Electricity Market Arrangements.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831788", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831787, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74643", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to the Modern Industrial Strategy, what recent progress he has made in delivering the STEP prototype fusion power station in West Burton.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831787", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831786, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74642", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, when he plans to publish plans for (a) civil and (b) defence nuclear collaboration.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831786", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831785, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74641", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, what work Great British Energy has undertaken with (a) Cambridgeshire and Peterborough Combined Auth", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831785", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831784, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74640", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, what progress he has made on strengthening connections to the EU energy market.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831784", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831783, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74639", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, which energy infrastructure projects will receive quicker pre-application periods from the reduction", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831783", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831782, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74638", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, what progress he has made on tackling high industrial electricity costs.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831782", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831781, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74637", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Afghans who (a) worked for British forces and (b) are dependents of people who worked for British forces were brought to the United Kingdom via the Afghan Response Route.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831781", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831780, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74636", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Afghan Response Route was included within data published on the Afghan Resettlement Programme.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831780", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831779, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74635", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the UK's Modern Industrial Strategy, published in June 2025, what progress he has made in launching an alliance with the High Value Manufacturing Catapult.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831779", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831778, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74634", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking with international partners to disrupt cross-jurisdictional fraud networks.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831778", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831777, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74633", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she is taking to help increase participation among the 18 \u2013 25 age group in forthcoming elections.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831777", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831776, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74632", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to uphold free speech in universities.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831776", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831775, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74631", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, what steps her Department is taking to ensure the prosecution of people who use AI to create deepfake photos of girls.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831775", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831774, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74630", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department funds research on chronic obstructive pulmonary disease and obesity.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831774", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831773, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-05T00:00:00", "uin": "74629", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress she has made on apprehending Kevin Thomas Parle.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831773", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831772, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74628", "questionText": "To ask the hon. Member for Perth and North Perthshire, representing the Members Estimate Committee, how much Representative Money has been made available to elected Members who have not taken the Oath in each year between 2006 and 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 91, "answeringBodyName": "Members Estimate Committee", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831772", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831771, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74627", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase the number of pupils learning languages in school.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831771", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831770, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74626", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what recent steps his Department has taken to support the development of carbon removal technologies ahead of the Autumn Budget.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831770", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831769, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74625", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of increasing the level of carbon removal on the UK's ability to meet it's net zero targets by (a) 2030 and (b) 2050.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831769", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831768, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74624", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that communities in (a) rural constituencies and (b) West Dorset constituency can easily access the SAFE European defence funds.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831768", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831767, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74623", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to support organisations in West Dorset to access the SAFE European defence funds.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831767", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831766, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74622", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the enforcement of existing regulations on e-bike use.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831766", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831765, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74621", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of people who have been diagnosed with Tinnitus in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831765", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831764, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74620", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of extreme weather events on West Dorset.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831764", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831763, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74619", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department plans to take steps to amend the regulation of genome-edited crops.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831763", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831762, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74618", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to support Dorset Council to identify potential brownfield sites for housing development.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831762", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831761, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74617", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will take steps to exempt domestic wine producers from wine duty rates.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831761", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831760, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74616", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to help tackle sexual abuse in prisons.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831760", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831759, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74615", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of obesity on cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831759", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831758, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74614", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to help reduce plastic pollution in (a) rivers, (b) seas and (c) other waterways.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831758", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831757, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74613", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions has she had with SEND service providers on Government proposals on SEND reform.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831757", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831756, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74612", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her expected timetable is for the (a) publication of the White Paper, (b) consultation and (c) implementation of reform on SEND provision in schools.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831756", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831755, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74611", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the (a) effectiveness and (b) timeliness of the delivery of EHCPs.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831755", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831754, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74610", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the potential impact of microplastics on health outcomes.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831754", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831753, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74609", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has been made of the potential impact of commercial greyhound racing on animal welfare.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831753", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831752, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74608", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent steps she has taken to help prevent people who have been sanctioned from concealing property assets in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831752", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831751, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74607", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate she has made of the number of property management companies that have (a) delivered services for and (b) made payments on behalf of sanctioned individuals fo", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831751", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831750, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74606", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has made a recent assessment of the potential impact of fly-tipping on private land owners.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831750", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831749, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74605", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with local authorities in (a) Slough and (b) the Thames Valley region on the implementation of mandatory digital waste tracking.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831749", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831748, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74604", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Environment Agency on trends in levels of fly-tipping in the (a) South East and (b) Slough.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831748", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831747, "askingMemberId": 4638, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74603", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent support she has provided to local authorities to help tackle fly-tipping.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831747", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831746, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74602", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has for the future use of properties utilised as Northern Ireland Points of Entry.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831746", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831703, "askingMemberId": 345, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "905507", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to increase the UK\u2019s amphibious capabilities.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831703", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831605, "askingMemberId": 4679, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74601", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, further to the Answer of 1 September 2025 to Question 69372 on Midland Main Line: Electrification, what is her Department's estimate of the cost of completing electrification of the Midland Main Line to Notting", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831605", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831604, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74600", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Border Force staff have been allocated to fast parcels in each of the last 10 financial years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831604", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831603, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74599", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has considered increasing funding for the Capital Grants scheme, in the context of levels of demand.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831603", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831602, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74598", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent steps her Department has taken to help reduce levels of reoffending in (a) South Norfolk constituency and (b) Norfolk.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831602", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831601, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74597", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to her Department's press release entitled Criminals to face football, travel, club and pub bans, published on 23 August 2025, what impact her Department estimates these measures will have on (a) r", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831601", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831600, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74596", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many assaults on (a) children and (b) staff have occurred in Young Offenders Institutions in each of the last 10 years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831600", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831599, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74595", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much staff time, in hours, was lost to sick leave in (a) the open estate, (b) the secure estate and (c) Young Offenders Institutions in each of the last 10 years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831599", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831598, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74594", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many neurodiversity support staff have been employed on the open and secure estate in each of the last 10 calendar years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831598", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831597, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74593", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of allowing inmates to apply for jobs in prison while on remand.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831597", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831596, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74592", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many psychologists have been employed on (a) the secure estate, (b) the open estate and (c) young offenders\u2019 institutions in each of the last 10 financial years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831596", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831595, "askingMemberId": 5205, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74591", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if her Department will make an assessment of the proportion of inmates on the women\u2019s estate who have immediate access to menstrual products in their cells.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831595", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831594, "askingMemberId": 5088, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74590", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of drivers who have repeatedly committed driving offences have received a lifetime driving ban.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831594", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831593, "askingMemberId": 5088, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74589", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of people convicted of death by dangerous driving did not pass the compulsory extended re-test in the last 12 months; and of these drivers, how many received a lifetime driving ban.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831593", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831592, "askingMemberId": 5088, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74588", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of people convicted of death by dangerous driving were given a lifetime driving ban in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831592", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831591, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74587", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July to Question 67336 on Crime, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of the Safer Streets Summer Initiative in reducing (a) town centre criminalit", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831591", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831590, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74586", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of adopting modes of English language assessment based on at-home proficiency tests within the planned Home Office English Languag", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831590", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831589, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74585", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department,  what assessment she has made of the potential impact of incorporating remote digital testing platforms into the forthcoming Home Office English Language Test contract on cybersecurity; and what steps", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831589", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831588, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74584", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential implications for his policies of Israel\u2019s involvement in the sectarian violence in southern Syria; and what assessment he has m", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831588", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831587, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74583", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions he has had with the interim Syrian authorities on (a) preventing human rights violations, (b) protecting all Syrians and (c) ending all forms of sectarian vi", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831587", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831586, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74582", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Government of Saudi Arabia on the reported rise in executions in relation to non-violent drug-related offences.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831586", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831585, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74581", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterpart in the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia on the reported increase in the use of (a) judicial and (b) non-judicial travel bans impose", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831585", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831584, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74580", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of further sanctions on Israel in response to (a) the humanitarian situation in Gaza and (b) plans for further illegal Isr", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831584", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831583, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74579", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the use of l non-SELT, unregulated English language tests for admission to UK higher education institutions on (a) universities and (b) students", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831583", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831582, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74578", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to her Mansion House speech on 15 July 2025, what deregulatory steps her Department has taken as part of the commitment to roll back regulations that have gone too far since 15 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831582", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831581, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74577", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she has taken to prevent (a) insolvent and (b) financially restricted organisations in the Aircraft Engineering Industry continuing to issue Certificates of Release to Service outside of effective re", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831581", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831580, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74576", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether Parliamentary time will be allocated for an annual debate to monitor progress towards achieving the goals set out in the animal welfare strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831580", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831579, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74575", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what discussions his Department has had with (a) the Department of Business and Trade and (b) the Cabinet office on ensuring its supply chains do not involve forced labour.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831579", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831578, "askingMemberId": 4942, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74574", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of recent reports of the shelling of civilian infrastructure in Thailand by Cambodian forces; and i", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831578", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831577, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74573", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to Sections 79-81 of the Building Safety Act 2022, how many buildings the Building Safety Regulator has (a) invited to submit a building assessment certificate app", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831577", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831576, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74572", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the press release entitled Reforms to Building Safety Regulator to accelerate housebuilding of 30 June 2025,  when she plans to (a) establish the new regulator ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831576", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831575, "askingMemberId": 1447, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74571", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what is her planned timetable for the Building Safety Regulator to determine the majority of building control applications within the regulator\u2019s statutory time frame.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831575", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831574, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74570", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to increase the number of staff working in nursery settings.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831574", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831573, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74569", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to increase the number of nursery places available for children in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831573", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831572, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74568", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has made an assessment of the adequacy of nursery places available for children in rural areas.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831572", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831571, "askingMemberId": 4934, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74567", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what data her Department holds on the (a) number and (b) availability of nursery places in (i) North Shropshire constituency and (ii) Shropshire.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831571", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831570, "askingMemberId": 5127, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74566", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his policies of the relationship between the Federal Government of Iraq and the Kurdistan Region of Iraq.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831570", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831569, "askingMemberId": 3935, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74565", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how his Department's capital budgets (a) were allocated in each financial year since 2023-24 and (b) have been allocated for each of the next five financial years.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831569", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831568, "askingMemberId": 3935, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74564", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average award is for pension credit claimants with a non-CTA immigration status.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831568", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831567, "askingMemberId": 4389, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74563", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to review the NICE guidelines on NHS-funded IVF treatment to allow for exceptions in cases where (a) short-term illness and (b) clinical advice from NHS staff has preve", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831567", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831566, "askingMemberId": 3935, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74562", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were in receipt of Pension Credit for each of the last five financial years, by immigration status.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831566", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831565, "askingMemberId": 5032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74561", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will make it her policy to start building a third track between York and Skelton Junction during this Parliament.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831565", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831564, "askingMemberId": 3935, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74560", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households were exempted from the benefit cap for the latest period for which data is available, by (a) reason for exemption and (b) amount they would otherwise have had capped.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831564", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831563, "askingMemberId": 4778, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74559", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of the firearms enquiry officers employed across police forces in England and Wales are warranted police officers.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831563", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831562, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74558", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of extending (a) free and (b) discounted bus travel to people under the age of 22; and what steps his Department is taking to ensure that young people in rura", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831562", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831561, "askingMemberId": 5172, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74557", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department plans to standardise the measure of vehicle sound testing in MOTs.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831561", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831560, "askingMemberId": 5172, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74556", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department plans to review proposals to tax pickup trucks as personal vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831560", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831559, "askingMemberId": 5172, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74555", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department plans to reintroduce measures to increase tax on higher polluting vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831559", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831558, "askingMemberId": 5172, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74554", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department plans to roll out noise detection cameras on roads.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831558", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831557, "askingMemberId": 4778, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74553", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many firearms enquiry officers are employed across police forces in England and Wales.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831557", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831556, "askingMemberId": 5171, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74552", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to help reduce the delays in decisions on Disability Living Allowance claims.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831556", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831555, "askingMemberId": 5171, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74551", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of the processing times of (a) applications for and (b) mandatory reconsiderations of Disability Living Allowance.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831555", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831554, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74550", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Children\u2019s Wellbeing and Schools Bill will prohibit the voluntary engagement of children as matchball assistants at grassroots football clubs.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831554", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831553, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74549", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to introduce targeted retention incentives for experienced teachers in addition to those offered to early-career teachers.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831553", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831552, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74548", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure schools have sufficient funding to retain experienced teachers alongside recruiting new staff.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831552", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831551, "askingMemberId": 4212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74547", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions she has had with The Pensions Regulator on strengthening its Code of Practice to require large companies running trust-based pension schemes to establish and maintain an internal audit ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831551", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831550, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74546", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Oral Statement of 1 September on Ukraine, Official Report columns 93-94, how many of the 200 electronic warfare and air defence systems delivered to Ukraine were manufactured in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831550", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831549, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74545", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Ministry of Defence budget was as a percentage of GDP in each of the last five financial years.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831549", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831548, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74544", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Oral Statement of 1 September on Ukraine, Official Report columns 93-94, how many of the 30 vehicles and engineering equipment delivered to Ukraine were manufactured in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831548", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831547, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74543", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Oral Statement of 01 September on Ukraine, Official Report columns 93-94, how many of 2,500 uncrewed platforms delivered to Ukraine were manufactured in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831547", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831546, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74542", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Oral Statement of 1 September on Ukraine, Official Report columns 93-94, how many of the 60,000 (a) artillery shells, (b) rockets and (c) missiles delivered to Ukraine were manufactured in t", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831546", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831545, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74541", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Oral Statement of 1 September on Ukraine, Official Report columns 93-94, how many of the 5 million rounds delivered to Ukraine were manufactured in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831545", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831544, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74540", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Oral Statement of 1 September on Ukraine, Official Report columns 93-94, whether urgent operational requirements are being considered as part of his review into armed forces readiness levels", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831544", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831543, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74539", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Oral Statement of 1 September on Ukraine, Official Report columns 93-94, when he expects to publish his review into armed forces readiness levels.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831543", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831542, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74538", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Oral Statement of 1 September on Ukraine, Official Report, columns 93-94, what his timeline is for the review into armed forces readiness levels.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831542", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831541, "askingMemberId": 4869, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74537", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the government of Saudi Arabia on the death sentences given to (a) Rami Gamal Shafik al-Najjar, (b) Ahmed Zeinhom Omar, (c", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831541", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831540, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74536", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of a licensing authority taking an extended period of time to accept or reject a private hire vehicle licence application.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831540", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831539, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74535", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the level of variation in the time taken to complete private hire vehicle licence applications across local authorities in England.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831539", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831538, "askingMemberId": 5223, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74534", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to deliver the national lung cancer screening programme by the target date of end of 2029-30.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831538", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831537, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74533", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what plans his Department has to provide (a) urgent aid and (b) longer-term climate adaptation support to Pakistan following recent floods.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831537", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831536, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74532", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 13 May 2025 to Question 49987, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that there is no funding gap between the end of Nature for Climate Peatland Grant", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831536", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831535, "askingMemberId": 5355, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74531", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many appointments to ministerial private offices since July 2024 have been made by civil service recruitment principles exceptions including the transfer of civil servants from other department", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831535", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831534, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74530", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department plans to take to support the horticultural industry in transitioning to peat-free growing.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831534", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831533, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74529", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to her Department's press release entitled Justice Secretary introduces democratic lock over Sentencing Council, published on 2 September 2025, what plans she has for enabling Parliament to (a) scr", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831533", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831532, "askingMemberId": 5032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74528", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of parents who are unable to take up or remain in employment because they have children with special educational needs and disabilities that do not have access a", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831532", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831531, "askingMemberId": 5164, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74527", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's press release entitled We\u2019re recruiting Asylum Decision Makers across the UK, published on 28 April 2025, how many asylum decisionmakers have been hired since 28 Apr", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831531", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831530, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74526", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to respond to Question 59818 on Defence: Public Expenditure, tabled on 13 June 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831530", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831529, "askingMemberId": 5032, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74525", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of extending the provision of Covid vaccinations to people with (a) type 1 diabetes and (b) long term immunosuppressive health conditions.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831529", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831528, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74524", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of (a) recognising and (b) including low-grade brain tumours in the forthcoming National Cancer Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831528", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831527, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74523", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he expects Ofwat's replacement to be in place.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831527", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831526, "askingMemberId": 4511, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74522", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the British Nationality (Irish Citizens) Act 2024, whether citizens who naturalised prior to 22 July 2025 will be included in the new registration route.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831526", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831525, "askingMemberId": 5284, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74521", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the final report of the Independent Water Commission, published on 21 July 2025, what progress he has made on implementing the recommendations of that report.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831525", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831524, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74520", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to equip local authorities to (a) identify and (b) appropriately respond to (i) United Front activity and (ii) transnational repression.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831524", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831523, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74519", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, in the context of Natural England no longer accepting complaints about the spread of injurious weeds, by what means the Weeds Act 1959 is now being enforced.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831523", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831522, "askingMemberId": 4511, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74518", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of protections for defendants under the Single Justice Procedure.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831522", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831521, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74517", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reason Natural England is no longer accepting complaints about the spread of injurious weeds.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831521", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831520, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74516", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what safeguards are in place to ensure that facial recognition technology used in supermarkets does not contribute to discriminatory outcomes based on race, gender, age, or disability.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831520", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831519, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74515", "questionText": "To ask the Leader of the House, with reference to the Government press release entitled Internship Scheme To Get More Working Class Students Into Civil Service, published on 1 August 2025, whether children of Hon. Members will be able to apply for the Sum", "answeringBodyId": 34, "answeringBodyName": "Leader of the House", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831519", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831518, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74514", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the evidential basis is for the Office for Value for Money making almost \u00a314 billion of annual efficiency gains by 2028-29 against planned day-to-day budgets for 2025-26.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831518", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831517, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74513", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has had discussions with civil liberties organisations on the use of facial recognition technology in commercial settings.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831517", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831516, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74512", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 29 August 2025 to Question 62335 on Senior Civil Service: Training, if he will list the external venues that have been authorised for hire since 4 April 2025; and the cost for each hire", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831516", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831515, "askingMemberId": 5320, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74511", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she plans to delay any local elections as a result of the new local government structures proposed in the English Devolution and Community Empowerment Bill.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831515", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831514, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74510", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the answer of 11 July 2025, to Question 64830, on Civil Service: Equality, whether his Department has consulted trade unions in relation to planned updates to the Guidance for Civil Service Staff Net", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831514", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831513, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74509", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his planned timetable is for updating the webpage entitled Salaries of members of His Majesty's Government on gov.uk.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831513", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831512, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74508", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, if his Department will issue guidance to retailers on ethical standards for the use of facial recognition technology.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831512", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831511, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74507", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the Transparency of Lobbying, Non-Party Campaigning and Trade Union Administration Act 2014.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831511", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831510, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74506", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Strategic Defence Review on the (a) budget and (b) headcount of the (i) UK Hydrographic Office and (ii) National Shipbuilding Office.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831510", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831509, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74505", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list all live maritime service contracts his Department has with subsidiaries of Serco Limited.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831509", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831508, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74504", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has issued guidance to retailers on the use of live facial recognition technology for (a) security and (b) commercial purposes.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831508", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831507, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74503", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) cost and (b) duration are for the contract between his Department and Serco Marine Services for the support vessels (i) SD Victoria and (ii) SD Northern River.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831507", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831506, "askingMemberId": 4511, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74502", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of the operation of the Prevent programme in schools.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831506", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831505, "askingMemberId": 3973, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74501", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the transfer of Stirling Castle from the Royal Fleet Auxillary to the Royal Navy on the operational capacity of the Royal Fleet Auxiliary.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831505", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831504, "askingMemberId": 4613, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74500", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Chief Secretary to the Prime Minister has any line management responsibilities for (a) civil servants and (b) special advisers in 10 Downing Street; and whether the (i) responsibilities and (ii) remi", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831504", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831503, "askingMemberId": 4511, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74499", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to help improve pay and conditions for court interpreters in the contracted service.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831503", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831502, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74498", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2025 to Question 61000 on Hunting, what recent progress he has made to ban trail-hunting.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831502", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831501, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74497", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list of all orders placed by each FLC on an Urgent Operational Requirements basis in relation to planning for potential Coalition of the Willing operations in Ukraine since such planning commenced by h", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831501", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831500, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74496", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2025 to Question 30304 on Gaza: Internally Displaced People, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people displaced fro", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831500", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831499, "askingMemberId": 5149, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74495", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help ensure that the potential impact on carers is taken into account in NICE\u2019s health technology appraisal decisions.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831499", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831498, "askingMemberId": 4511, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74494", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Independent Technical Review of Qualifications and Experience Requirements for the Provision of Spoken Language Interpreting of 17 March 2025, what steps her Department is taking to help ens", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831498", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831497, "askingMemberId": 5149, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74493", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to review the manner in which NICE considers carer-related quality of life in its assessments of treatments for (a) rare, (b) progressive and (c) paediatric diseases.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831497", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831496, "askingMemberId": 5149, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74492", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help ensure that NICE appraisal decisions for (a) progressive and (b) degenerative diseases are taken in a timely manner. .", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831496", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831495, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74491", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June to Question 59824 on Gaza: Humanitarian Aid, whether his Department has had discussions with the International Maritime Organisation on the ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831495", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831494, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74490", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June to Question 59825 on Gaza: Humanitarian Aid, what diplomatic steps his Department has taken to help ensure freedom of navigation in the East", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831494", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831493, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74489", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much of the \u00a350 million allocated for targeted motor neurone disease research has been allocated as of September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831493", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831492, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74488", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to support research into motor neurone disease.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831492", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831491, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74487", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to increase support available for people with neurological conditions.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831491", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831490, "askingMemberId": 5220, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74486", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that visa applications for injured Palestinian children are processed without delay; and whether those visas applications can be fast-tracked.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831490", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831489, "askingMemberId": 5086, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74485", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the budget is for the Office of the Standing Advocate in financial years (a) 2025-26 and (b) 2026-27.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831489", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831488, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74484", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the current Child Maintenance Service income-based model on middle-income paying parents.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831488", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831487, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74483", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of the planned \u00a329 billion annual increase in the NHS budget over the next three years will be allocated to children\u2019s palliative care services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831487", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831486, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74482", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to undertake a comprehensive review of the (a) planning, (b) commissioning and (c) funding of children\u2019s palliative care in South Suffolk.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831486", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831485, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74481", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to extend the NHS England Children\u2019s Hospice Grant beyond the 2025-26 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831485", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831484, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74480", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the \u00a326 million NHS England Children\u2019s Hospice Grant for meeting the costs faced by children\u2019s hospices in South Suffolk.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831484", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831483, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74479", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many pubs have closed each year since 2015.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831483", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831482, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74478", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has provided funding to the Centre for Hate Studies at the University of Leicester.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831482", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831481, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74477", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has has made of the potential impact of the the suspension of refugee family reunion route on number of visa applications.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831481", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831480, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74476", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been (a) arrested, (b) charged and (c) convicted for social media posts in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831480", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831479, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74475", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of increasing English language requirements for non-UK staff within the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831479", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831478, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74474", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether his Department is taking steps to help (a) increase recruitment and (b) tackle staffing shortages in the hospitality sector in (a) towns, (b) rural communities and (c) other places in (i) Somer", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831478", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831477, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74473", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to help support the local hospitality sector to regenerate high streets in (a) Yeovil, (b) Chard and (c) other towns.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831477", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831476, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74472", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate she has make of the potential impact of the requirement for letting agents to carry out money laundering checks on landlords and tenants on the number of rental pro", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831476", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831475, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74471", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to help support landlords to ensure their properties comply with the Decent Homes Standard.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831475", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831474, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74470", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of rising energy costs on small to medium sized hospitality businesses in Yeovil constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831474", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831473, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74469", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she plans to take to support landlords to meet the deadline for all rental properties to have an EPC C minimum rating by 2030.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831473", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831472, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74468", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions her Department has had with industry bodies on strengthening (a) apprenticeships and (b) training routes in the hospitality sector to support small and medium-sized businesses in Yeovil constit", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831472", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831471, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74467", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will consider increasing the \u00a3450,000 cap for buying a first property with a Lifetime ISA in line with property price inflation.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831471", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831470, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74466", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of the level of (a) Value Added Tax rates and (b) business rates on the recovery of hospitality businesses in rural areas in Yeovil constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831470", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831469, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74465", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she has considered introducing additional measures to support first-time buyers.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831469", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831468, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74464", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what support is available for first-time buyers in Cornwall.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831468", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831467, "askingMemberId": 5293, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74463", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make his policy to introduce a Long service and good conduct medal for (a) doctors and (b) nurses.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831467", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831466, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74462", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to section 28 of the Youth Justice and Criminal Justice Act 1999, whether she has had discussions with the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Women and Safeguarding on the use of pre-record", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831466", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831465, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74461", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to Section 28 of the Youth Justice and Criminal Evidence Act 1999, what steps she is taking to ensure that (a) victims and (b) witnesses are supported following their pre-recorded evidence.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831465", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831464, "askingMemberId": 4074, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74460", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to section 28 of the Youth Justice and Criminal Justice Act 1999, what steps she is taking to ensure court proceedings in sexual cases are not repeatedly adjourned.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831464", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831463, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74459", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to inform veterans who served in Northern Ireland of the Victims Pension Scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831463", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831462, "askingMemberId": 5334, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-11T00:00:00", "uin": "74458", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the reduction in the post-decision move on period on levels of homelessness.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831462", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831461, "askingMemberId": 4869, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74457", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she consulted people with direct experience of the immigration system prior to designing the (a) settlement and (b) citizenship changes proposed in the Immigration White Paper.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831461", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831460, "askingMemberId": 5242, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-15T00:00:00", "uin": "74456", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to support social housing tenants affected by the transition from Employment and Support Allowance to Universal Credit.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831460", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831459, "askingMemberId": 4126, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74455", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she has made an assessment of the affordability of ground rents in Newcastle upon Tyne East and Wallsend constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831459", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831458, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74454", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has made a recent assessment of the level of efficiency across government in answering correspondence from members of the public.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831458", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831457, "askingMemberId": 4736, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74453", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the (a) Bank of England and (b) Financial Conduct Authority have a role in the (i) authorisation and (ii) regulation of bond sales (A) by and (B) on behalf of the Development Company for Israel in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831457", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831456, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74452", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate her Department has made of the average wait time for callers to HMRC helplines; and what steps her Department is taking to reduce waiting times for callers to HMRC helplines.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831456", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831455, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74451", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions he has had with European counterparts on export tariffs for the British Overseas Territories.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831455", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831454, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74450", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department produced an impact assessment prior to the Supreme Court judgment in DELTA Merseyside Ltd v Uber Britannia Ltd on the application of VAT to private hire vehicle journeys.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831454", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831453, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74449", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support state-level institutions in Bosnia and Herzegovina.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831453", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831452, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74448", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she plans to take to ensure that rail workers maintain their (a) pay and (b) working conditions when their rail company is moved into public ownership.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831452", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831451, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74447", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when she plans to publish a response to her Department's consultation entitled Consultation on the VAT Treatment of Private Hire Vehicles, which closed on 8 August 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831451", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831450, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74446", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to her Department's consultation entitled Consultation on the VAT Treatment of Private Hire Vehicles, which closed on 8 August 2024, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831450", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831449, "askingMemberId": 4434, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74445", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what discussions he has had with European counterparts on offering support to Bosnia and Herzegovina on the rule of law.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831449", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831448, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74444", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to impose VAT at 20% on all private hire fares.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831448", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831447, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74443", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will publish the membership and terms of reference of the Rail Engagement Group.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831447", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831446, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74442", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she plans to have discussions with unions ahead of rail companies being taken into public ownership.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831446", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831445, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74441", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential need to improve screening for hypermobility in neurodivergent individuals.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831445", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831444, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74440", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to increase (a) awareness and (b) understanding of the association between (i) hypermobility and (ii) neurodivergence in the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831444", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831443, "askingMemberId": 5191, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74439", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential links between hypermobility and neurodivergence.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831443", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831442, "askingMemberId": 5299, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-10T00:00:00", "uin": "74438", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with international counterparts on compliance with international humanitarian law in relation to access of Gazan civilians to water.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831442", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831441, "askingMemberId": 5299, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-10T00:00:00", "uin": "74437", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support the cholera response in Sudan.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831441", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831440, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-11T00:00:00", "uin": "74436", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent analysis she has made of the potential impact on the economy of Lifetime ISA savers defering utilising the scheme for purchasing houses due to the house price restriction and withdrawal penalty.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831440", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831439, "askingMemberId": 5103, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74435", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions she has had with (a) Citizens Advice, (b) disabled people and (c) carers as part of the upcoming Timms Review.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831439", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831438, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74434", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Saudi Arabian counterparts on its use of capital punishment in (a) non-lethal criminal cases and (b) other criminal cases.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831438", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831437, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74433", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients with (a) leukaemia and lymphoma, (b) myeloma, (c) other cancers, (d) myelodysplastic syndromes, (e) aplastic anemia, (f) thalassemia, (g) bleeding disorders and (h) other conditio", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831437", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831436, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74432", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many sickle cell patients who had complications due to sickle cell listed as their cause of death experienced haemolysis in the period before their death in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831436", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831435, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74431", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many sickle cell patients whose cause of death was listed as complications due to sickle cell have had an inquest into their death.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831435", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831434, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74430", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether it is NHS policy to carry out an inquest if a patient dies within 48 hours of being admitted to hospital.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831434", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831433, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74429", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many sickle cell patients have died due to complications due to sickle cell in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831433", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831432, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74428", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, , how many sickle cell patients have developed haemolysis due to receiving a blood transfusion with unmatched blood during the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831432", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831431, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74427", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with the NHS on its policy of informing Sickle Cell patients when they are not given Ro matched blood.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831431", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831430, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74426", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will ensure that (a) prioritisation for medical evacuation and treatment of children from Gaza is based solely on clinical urgency and medical need and (b) it is not contingent on the availab", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831430", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831429, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74425", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of increasing the number of critically injured Palestinian children that are permitted into the UK for life-saving medical treatment.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831429", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831428, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74424", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to waive biometric requirements for children medically evacuated from Gaza to the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831428", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831427, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74423", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to help ensure that children evacuated from Gaza for medical treatment are accompanied by appropriate family members.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831427", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831426, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74422", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to help ensure that children medically evacuated from Gaza will not be subject to forced return to (a) Gaza or (b) an unsafe country following treatment in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831426", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831425, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74421", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to help increase participation in women's rugby.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831425", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831424, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74420", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of the wholesale price increase of Mounjaro on patients managing (a) obesity and (b) type 2 diabetes.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831424", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831423, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74419", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to help increase girl\u2019s participation in rugby.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831423", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831422, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74418", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate her Department has made of the number of young people in supported accommodation who have (a) reduced working hours and (b) turned down employment opportunities due to the tapering ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831422", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831421, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74417", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she plans to review the housing benefits earnings disregard threshold for individuals in supported accommodation.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831421", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831420, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74416", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department plans to take to support (a) lower income families and (b) pensioners impacted by the energy price cap increase.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831420", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831419, "askingMemberId": 4764, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74415", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on aligning the Housing Benefit taper rate with the Universal Credit taper rate for young people in supported accommodation", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831419", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831418, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74414", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the red delivery confidence rating for the Type 31 frigate programme on the (a) overall user requirements and (b) operational readiness of the Royal Navy.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831418", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831417, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74413", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what risks he has identified in the complex integration challenges for the Type 31 frigate programme; and what (a) technical and (b) contractual steps he is taking to help mitigate those risks.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831417", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831416, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74412", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to meet the first-of-class schedule for the Type 31 frigate.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831416", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831415, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74411", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the additional costs arising from inflation on the Type 31 frigate programme.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831415", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831414, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74410", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what measures are outlined in the pending Review Note to transition the Protector programme from red to green delivery confidence rating; and what (a) timelines and (b) oversight mechanisms are in place to ensure", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831414", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831413, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74409", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the withdrawal of government funding for Global Citizenship Education in England on the provision of Global Citizenship Education programmes.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831413", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831412, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74408", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure schools reach Sustainable Development Goal 4.7.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831412", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831411, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74407", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason the Protector programme has a red delivery confidence rating.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831411", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831410, "askingMemberId": 1444, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74406", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his planned timetable is for approval of the Review Note for the Protector programme.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831410", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831409, "askingMemberId": 4371, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74405", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what representations he has made to his Honduran counterpart on the killing of Juan L\u00f3pez.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831409", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831408, "askingMemberId": 4464, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74404", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of the Approved Mileage Allowance Payments rate; and whether she plans to update that rate.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831408", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831407, "askingMemberId": 4464, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74403", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of the Skilled Worker visa salary threshold on the ability of veterinary practices to recruit staff; and what appeals process is a", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831407", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831406, "askingMemberId": 4464, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74402", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the minimum salary requirement is for overseas-qualified veterinary surgeons to be eligible for Skilled Worker visas.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831406", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831405, "askingMemberId": 5128, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74401", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of existing levels of central government funding for fire and rescue services.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831405", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831404, "askingMemberId": 5342, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74400", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of the amount jurors can claim for jury service in the context of trends in the level of childcare costs in the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831404", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831403, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74399", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department holds contracts with Straight Flight Nevada Commercial Leasing LLC.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831403", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831402, "askingMemberId": 5302, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74398", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of the extension of permitted days for temporary campsites on licensed campsite operators; and what steps she is taking to ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831402", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831401, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74397", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department has had recent discussions with Starlink on satellite services for trains.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831401", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831400, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74396", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of satellite technology on (a) mobile and (b) internet connectivity on long-distance rail services between Scotland and London.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831400", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831399, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74395", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to improve mobile and internet connectivity on long-distance rail services between Scotland and London.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831399", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831398, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74394", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 3 March 2025 to Question 31168 on Primodos: Research and with reference to the oral contribution of Mr Roland Moyle on 26 May 1978, HC official record Volume 950, whether ", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831398", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831397, "askingMemberId": 152, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74393", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, when he last raised the case of Jimmy Lai with US counterparts.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831397", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831396, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74392", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2025 to Question 64094 on Chagos Islands: Sovereignty, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of publishing the payments to Ma", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831396", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831395, "askingMemberId": 4571, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74391", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether she plans to remove the sanction of imprisonment for non-payment of Council Tax in England as part of wider proposed sentencing reforms.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831395", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831394, "askingMemberId": 5257, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74390", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the Dental Act 1921 in meeting patient needs in orthodontic care.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831394", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831393, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74389", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the introduction of VAT on independent school fees on the ability on non-affluent families to afford private school education.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831393", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831392, "askingMemberId": 5257, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74388", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she plans to address leasehold issues arising from probate sales of properties which did not qualify for cladding remediation support under the Building Safety Act (2022)", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831392", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831391, "askingMemberId": 5220, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74387", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to review the definition of recycled in Section 49 of the Finance Act 2021 to recognize organic recycling through food waste schemes.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831391", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831390, "askingMemberId": 5220, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74386", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of soft plastic recycling schemes operated by supermarkets.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831390", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831389, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74385", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of revising the compensation scheme for electricity consumers to include compensation for the inconvenience caused by power cuts of s", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831389", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831388, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74384", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she last met the (a) Rugby Football Union and (b) Premiership Rugby; and what issues were discussed.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831388", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831387, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74383", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps he is taking to help (a) ensure that energy consumers receive a reliable electricity supply and (b) reduce power cuts due to issues with the electricity distribution network.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831387", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831386, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74382", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an estimate of the cost to the police of (a) kennelling and (b) court fees for dogs subject to seized dog cases.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831386", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831385, "askingMemberId": 5296, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74381", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment she has made of the potential impact of the tax-free childcare system on levels of administration for early years providers.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831385", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831384, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74380", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many allotment sites have been sold by local authorities with permission from her Department since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831384", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831383, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74379", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Allotment Act 1925 for protecting allotments from being sold by local authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831383", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831382, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74378", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of Section 23 of the Small Holdings and Allotments Act 1908 for ensuring that (a) district and (b) parish councils provide allot", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831382", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831381, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74377", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his planned timetable is for banning heated tobacco adverts following the Royal Assent of the Tobacco and Vapes Bill; and if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forw", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831381", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831380, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74376", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions her Department has held with railway trade unions on transfers of employment to DfT Operator Limited.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831380", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831379, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74375", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he expects the Tobacco and Vapes Bill to receive Royal Assent.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831379", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831378, "askingMemberId": 4005, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74374", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will set out the scope the proposed ban on trophy hunting imports.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831378", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831377, "askingMemberId": 5220, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74373", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent guidance his Department has provided to local authorities on the (a) collection and (b) disposal of independently certified BS 13432 compliant compostable packaging.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831377", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831376, "askingMemberId": 5220, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74372", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with UKRI on steps his Department is taking to support innovative materials whose development has been funded by grants from Innovate UK.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831376", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831375, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74371", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent progress his Department has made on the implementation of the Oliver McGowan mandatory training on learning disability and autism across the NHS and social care workforce.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831375", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831374, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74370", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of Homes England\u2019s management of the (a) Techforest and (b) Woolmead sites in Farnham and Bordon constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831374", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831373, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74369", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has conducted a risk or opportunity assessment of the potential strategic use of seized Bitcoin assets as part of the UK's financial reserves.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831373", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831372, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74368", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential long-term fiscal merits of retaining the Bitcoins held by UK authorities in connection with investment fraud.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831372", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831371, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74367", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of changes to the licensing system for Section 2 shotguns on rural economies.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831371", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831370, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74366", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department is taking to (a) monitor and (b) help prevent the online sale of products containing asbestos; and whether the Health and Safety Executive has issued recent (i) enforcement ac", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831370", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831369, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74365", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of amending the rules for the childcare vouchers scheme to allow participants to receive refunds, subject to the appropriate tax and National Insurance contributi", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831369", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831368, "askingMemberId": 5010, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74364", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has for the Holiday activities and food programme after 31 March 2026.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831368", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831367, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74363", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of establishing an Older People\u2019s Commissioner for England.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831367", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831366, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74362", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of bank branch closures on older people\u2019s access to cash.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831366", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831365, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74361", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the availability of Enhertu for the treatment of (a) HER2-positive and (b) HER2-low breast cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831365", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831364, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74360", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that people impacted by (a) long-term health conditions and (b) disabilities are consulted during the review of changes to Personal Independence Payment.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831364", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831363, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74359", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what diplomatic steps he is taking to help ensure enforcement of international humanitarian law protections for journalists in Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831363", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831362, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74358", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was spent on legal aid for asylum cases in each year since 2019.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831362", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831361, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74357", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse was of the (a) evacuation and (b) relocation of Palestinian students from Gaza to the UK in 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831361", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831360, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74356", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what the projected cost to the public purse is of Chevening scholarships awarded to students from Gaza for 2025-26.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831360", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831359, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74355", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many child benefit claims were cancelled because the claimant was found to be living abroad in each year since 2020.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831359", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831358, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74354", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of adult social care on supporting people of working age into the labour market.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831358", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831357, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74353", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of her Department\u2019s fair funding review for local authorities on adult social care provision for people of working age.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831357", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831356, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74352", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking with devolved Administrations to help reduce waiting times from GP referral to first routine dermatology appointments.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831356", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831355, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74351", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she plans to provide financial support to maintain long wave radio services.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831355", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831354, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74350", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with Baroness Casey on how sector stakeholders can engage with the commission on adult social care.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831354", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831353, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74349", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of maintaining long wave radio transmission infrastructure on (a) national resilience and (b) strategic defence.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831353", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831352, "askingMemberId": 5170, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74348", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking with international allies to help bring greater stability to Syria.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831352", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831351, "askingMemberId": 5170, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74347", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what steps he is taking with international allies to help bring greater stability to Lebanon.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831351", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831350, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74346", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what his policy is on the (a) storage, (b) retention and (c) use of data collected from social media monitoring activities by (i) government departments and (ii) affiliated agencies.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831350", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831349, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74345", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the cost to the public purse was of investigating unlicensed fishing by the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831349", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831348, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74344", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will publish a breakdown of Personal Independence Payment claimants by (a) nationality and (b) immigration status in each year since 2020.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831348", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831347, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74343", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether any third-party contractors have been engaged to assist with the monitoring of social media content.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831347", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831346, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74342", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what oversight mechanisms are in place to ensure that government monitoring of public social media content does not infringe upon freedom of expression and privacy rights.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831346", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831345, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74341", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether a new (a) memorandum of understanding and (b) facility agreement is being agreed between her Department and its agencies with the Greater Manchester Combined Authority in", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831345", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831344, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74340", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what representations he has received on increasing permitted development rights for onshore wind turbines to 30 metres.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831344", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831343, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74339", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she plans to consult on the repeal of Strategic Environmental Assessments and Environmental Impact Assessments regime.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831343", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831342, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74338", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will publish the (a) allotment disposal application and (b) allotment disposal consent by the Secretary of State for the Ravenscroft Allotments in Horsham.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831342", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831341, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74337", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2025 to Question 66192 on Emergency Services: Employers' Contributions, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of basing allocatio", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831341", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831340, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74336", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the abolition of fixed term tenancies on the security of tenure for rental properties for those who needed to be in an are", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831340", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831339, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74335", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department holds information on (a) the total number of allotments in England and (b) the number of allotments by local authority.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831339", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831338, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74334", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, for what purposes government agencies monitor social media activity by members of the public; and whether there are limits on the scope of such monitoring.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831338", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831337, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74333", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what planning (a) policies and (b) guidance her Department has issued on council farms.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831337", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831336, "askingMemberId": 5351, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74332", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the (a) number and (b) nature of instances in which members of the public have been subject to monitoring by government agencies on social media platforms in t", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831336", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831335, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74331", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she plans to introduce (a) schemes and (b) fiscal incentives to help first-time buyers onto the housing ladder.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831335", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831334, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74330", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans she has to provide funding for councils to support long-term empty homes being put back into use.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831334", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831333, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74329", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of housebuilding on the land designated as industrial at Old Oak Common.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831333", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831332, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74328", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to support local authorities in effectively managing (a) waste disposal, (b) water pollution and (c) other environmental and public safety iss", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831332", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831331, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74327", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what her planned timetable is for the introduction of National Development Management Policies; and whether she has made changes to the policy developed by the previous Administr", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831331", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831330, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74326", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate she has made of the total council tax receipts in England from 2024-25 and each subsequent year of the spending review.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831330", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831329, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74325", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 1 April 2025 to Question 38374 on Economic Activity of Public Bodies (Overseas Matters) Bill, what assessment her Department made of the potential impac", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831329", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831328, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74324", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, further to her Department's press release of 17 June 2025 entitled Over 500,000 homes to be built through new National Housing Bank, what is her planned timetable for the financi", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831328", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831327, "askingMemberId": 4630, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74323", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July to Question\u00a064209 on Western Sahara: Human Rights, whether he has had discussions with his counterpart in Morocco on the details of what auto", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831327", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831326, "askingMemberId": 4630, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74322", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he plans to increase the provision of aid to the Sahrawi refugee camps, following the UN Secretary General\u2019s report entitled Question of Western Sahara of 31 July 202", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831326", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831325, "askingMemberId": 4630, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74321", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will have discussions with his Moroccan counterpart on the blocking of visits by the Office of the United Nations High Commissioner for Human Rights to occupied Western", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831325", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831324, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74320", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will provide an estimate of the total number of Gazans that will enter the asylum system following medical treatment in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831324", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831323, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74319", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what the total cost to the public purse is for the evacuation of children from Gaza as of 2 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831323", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831322, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74318", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, whether her Department has spent money on promotion through social media influencers since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831322", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831321, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74317", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether his Department has spent money on promotion through social media influencers since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831321", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831320, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74316", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people who were applying for asylum have been issued with a driving licence since 2020.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831320", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831319, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74315", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether his Department has spent money on promotion through social media influencers since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831319", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831318, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74314", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether his Department has spent money on promotion through social media influencers since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831318", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831317, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74313", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of prisoners released under the early release scheme have subsequently been (a) rearrested, (b) charged and (c) convicted of other offences.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831317", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831316, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74312", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether her Department has spent money on promotion through social media influencers since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 28, "answeringBodyName": "Wales Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831316", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831315, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74311", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether his Department has spent money on promotion through social media influencers since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831315", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831314, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74310", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has spent money on promotion through social media influencers since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831314", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831313, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74309", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has spent money on promotion through social media influencers since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831313", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831312, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74308", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department has spent money on promotion through social media influencers since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831312", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831311, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74307", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps their Department is taking to implement the guidance entitled The government\u2019s approach to rural proofing 2025, published on 15 May 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831311", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831310, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74306", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether her Department has spent money on promotion through social media influencers since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831310", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831309, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74305", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps their Department is taking to implement the guidance entitled The government\u2019s approach to rural proofing 2025, published on 15 May 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831309", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831308, "askingMemberId": 5158, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74304", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the number of staff working in her Department, broken down by nationality.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831308", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831307, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74303", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people with disabilities were employed in her Department on 2 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831307", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831306, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74302", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people with disabilities were employed in his Department on 2 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831306", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831305, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74301", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how many people with disabilities were employed in his Department on 2 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831305", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831304, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74300", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how many people with disabilities were employed in his Department on 2 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831304", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831303, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74299", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people with disabilities were employed in her Department on 2 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831303", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831302, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74298", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many people with disabilities were employed in his Department on 2 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831302", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831301, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74297", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people with disabilities were employed in his Department on 2 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831301", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831300, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74296", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people with disabilities were employed in his Department on 2 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831300", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831299, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74295", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many people with disabilities were employed in his Department on 2 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831299", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831298, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74294", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many people with disabilities were employed in her Department on 2 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831298", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831297, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74293", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people with disabilities were employed in her Department on 2 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831297", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831296, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74292", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with disabilities were employed in her Department on 2 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831296", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831295, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74291", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many people with disabilities were employed in her Department on 2 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831295", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831294, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74290", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people with disabilities were employed in her Department on 2 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831294", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831293, "askingMemberId": 4995, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74289", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of no rollover option being in place for the Countryside Stewardship scheme on (a) farmers and (b) 2030 nature recovery targets.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831293", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831292, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74288", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking to help increase the number of people employed by the Government Social Research Profession in Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831292", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831291, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74287", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much her Department has allocated (a) overall, (b) to the Ministry of Defence and (c) to the Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office to fund payments under the UK/Mauritius: Agreement concerning the Chagos ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831291", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831290, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74286", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many times the Treasury Board has met since 4 July 2024; and on what dates she attended.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831290", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831289, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74285", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Business Engagement Lead is a (a) special adviser, (b) direct ministerial appointment, (c) civil servant appointed by open and fair competition and (d) civil servant appointed by recruitment principles e", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831289", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831288, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74284", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment (a) HM Treasury and (b) the Government Actuary Department has made of the accuracy of the GDP deflator forecasts by the Office for Budget Responsibility.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831288", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831287, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74283", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of progress on reducing NHS waiting lists in North East Somerset and Hanham constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831287", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831286, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74282", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of progress in transitioning to net zero across the economy.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831286", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831285, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74281", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of progress towards making the UK a clean energy superpower.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831285", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831284, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74280", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the press release entitled Internship Scheme To Get More Working Class Students Into Civil Service, published on 1 August 2025, whether children of (a) NHS doctors and (b) NHS nur", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831284", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831283, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74279", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the press release entitled Internship Scheme To Get More Working Class Students Into Civil Service, published on 1 August 2025, whether prison wardens are defined as working class, for the purp", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831283", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831282, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74278", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the students from Gaza granted permission to study in the United Kingdom under the Chevening scheme will be subject to any security checks or vetting.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831282", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831281, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74277", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 22 August 2025 to Question 69070 on Syria: Inter Mediate, what meetings the Prime Minister\u2019s National Security Adviser has had with Inter Mediate.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831281", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831280, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74276", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost to the public purse was of each official reception in 10 Downing Street since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831280", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831279, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74275", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the iphones provided to No.10 staff use a Virtual Private Network.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831279", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831278, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74274", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the name of each of the Prime Minister's (a) special representatives, (b) envoys and (c) direct ministerial appointments who were in post on 2 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831278", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831277, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74273", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 May 2025 to Question 51154, if he will publish the declaration by the Ambassador to the United States of America.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831277", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831276, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74272", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, in what circumstances would the (a) Mauritius and (b) UK Government be able to terminate the UK/Mauritius: Agreement concerning the Chagos Archipelago including Diego Garcia ", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831276", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831275, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74271", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of what the pull-factors are that are encouraging illegal immigration to the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831275", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831274, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74270", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his interview with the BBC on 15 August 2025 regarding a potential post-ceasefire UK military presence in Ukraine, which UK forces would be deployed to the region; and which are ready to act fro", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831274", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831273, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74269", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the UK-France one-in, one-out pilot scheme signed on 4 August 2025, what (a) security checks and (b) acceptance criteria are applied to asylum seekers accepted to the UK under the te", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831273", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831272, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74268", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether cultural access to science falls within the remit of her Department, in the context of the UK's obligations under (a) Article 27 of the Universal Declaration of Human Rights and (b) Artic", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831272", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831271, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74267", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether science and discovery centres fall within the remit of her Department.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831271", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831270, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74266", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the swing bridge is eligible for repair funding from the National Lottery.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831270", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831269, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74265", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many and what proportion of full-time equivalent staff in her Department work on the (a) promotion and (b) preservation of industrial heritage; whether industrial heritage sites are eligible ", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831269", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831268, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74264", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether he science and discovery centres fall within the remit of his Department.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831268", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831267, "askingMemberId": 4124, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74263", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what steps he is taking with Cabinet colleagues to provide funding for research into the (a) prevention and (b) treatment of arthritis and musculoskeletal disease in UK universities.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831267", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831266, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74262", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the press release entitled Government protects thousands of miles of bus services from being scrapped, published on 3 June 2025, whether her Department plans to provide additional funding to l", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831266", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831265, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74261", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the national distribution of the length of time between the date on which developers and local authorities agree funding under section 106 of th", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831265", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831264, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74260", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of reforms to Level 7 apprenticeships on the Pathways to Planning programme.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831264", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831263, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74259", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement on Local Government Reorganisation of 3 June 2025,  HCWS676, for what reason Bedfordshire has not received funding to support development ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831263", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831262, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74258", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to page 19 of the report entitled New Towns for England, published by WPI Strategy in May 2025, which funding model the Government is considering.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831262", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831261, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74257", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to page 3 of the report entitled New Towns for England, published by WPI Strategy in May 2025, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of modula", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831261", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831260, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74256", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to page 2 of the the report entitled New Towns for England, published by WPI Strategy in May 2025, whether her Department has made an assessment of the accuracy of", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831260", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831259, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74255", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will conduct a lessons learned review from the initial period of the decision to withdraw universal Winter Fuel Payments.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831259", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831258, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74254", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to support employment in the production of Sustainable Aviation Fuels.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831258", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831257, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74253", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of increasing the pension credit threshold.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831257", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831256, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74252", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential implications for her policies of the findings of the report entitled Impact of changes to the UK non-domiciled regime, published by the Centre for Econo", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831256", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831255, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74251", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential impact of changes to Agricultural and Business Property Relief on the economy of the East of England.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831255", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831254, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74250", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential implications for her policies of the findings of the report entitled Taxing Futures: The economic and fiscal implications of changes to BPR & APR for UK", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831254", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831253, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74249", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the impact of her Budget in 2024 on the performance of AIM shares.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831253", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831252, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74248", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 May 2025 to Question 49823 on Air Passenger Duty: Economic Growth, if she will estimate the potential impact of higher rates of Air Passenger Duty on the number of flights taken.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831252", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831251, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74247", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of reducing funding for Natural England's programme to (a) designate and (b) expand National Landscapes on economic growth.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831251", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831250, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74246", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she plans reforms to encourage (a) investment and (b) growth in the (i) beer and (ii) pub sector.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831250", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831249, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74245", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will make an assessment of the long-term economic benefits of permanently reducing the business rates multiplier for the (a) beer and (b) pub sectors.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831249", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831248, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74244", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that business rates reform supports regional economic growth in (a) rural and (b) coastal areas.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831248", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831247, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74243", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of increasing the tax rate paid by bookmakers to align it with the online gaming tax rate on Huntingdon Racecourse.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831247", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831246, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74242", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 1 September 2025 to Question 69521 on Ajax Vehicles: Procurement, what will be the distribution of the 93 Ares vehicles across units.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831246", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831245, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74241", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 1 September 2025 to Question 69515 on Typhoon Aircraft: Decommissioning, what roles the four Tranche 1 Typhoons are conducting.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831245", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831244, "askingMemberId": 5264, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74240", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to publish the outcome of the Police Activity Survey; and what plans she has to conduct a further such survey.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831244", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831243, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74239", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many child deaths were recorded where parental consanguinity was (a) identified and (b) not identified in England in each year since 2019.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831243", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831242, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74238", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the availability of ultrasound scans to pregnant women who (a) report reduced foetal movement before 28 weeks\u2019 gestation and (b) present on more th", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831242", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831241, "askingMemberId": 5341, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74237", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of routinely (a) recording and (b) reporting the number of animals bred for and not used in scientific research.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831241", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831240, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74236", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she will take steps to improve transparency in the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency\u2019s decision-making process for over-70s driving licence renewals; and what weightings are given to recent eyesight tests ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831240", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831239, "askingMemberId": 4769, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74235", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to enable Hertfordshire and West Essex ICB to allow GP to make referrals to adult ADHD assessment waiting lists.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831239", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831238, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74234", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment has the government made of the impact of increasing the cap on a single bus fare from \u00a32 to \u00a33 on bus journeys across England.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831238", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831237, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74233", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has had recent discussions with the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport on taking steps to help ensure that transport links are adequate to support funding for cricket facilities at The ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831237", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831236, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74232", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to develop an effective vaccine for bluetongue virus serotype 3.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831236", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831235, "askingMemberId": 5218, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74231", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to support children who arrive at school by (a) state-provided buses and (b) taxis to make use of free breakfast clubs.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831235", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831234, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74230", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the report from the Child Poverty Action Group entitled 'Two-child limit statistics briefing', published on 10 July 2025, what steps she is taking to lift children out of poverty.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831234", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831233, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74229", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential impact of abolishing the two-child benefit cap on children in poverty.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831233", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831232, "askingMemberId": 5348, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74228", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department\u2019s policies of the report by Action on Smoking and Health entitled At risk? Tobacco dependence treatment in the NHS, published on 2", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831232", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831231, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74227", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department encouraged the Tunisian government to set up complaint mechanisms for people to report alleged violations of their human rights as part of the implementation of (a) the upskilli", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831231", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831230, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74226", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the potential implications for his policies of the findings by the Human Rights Watch entitled Questions and Answers on Israel\u2019s Use of W", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831230", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831229, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74225", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has met with representatives from Red Tractor to discuss the effectiveness of the Red Tractor assurance scheme regarding animal welfare standards.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831229", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831228, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74224", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, whether he plans to raise the potential impact of Chinese companies providing military support to Russia during his upcoming trade talks with China.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831228", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831227, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74223", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department holds contracts with Straight Flight Nevada Commercial Leasing LLC.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831227", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831226, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-05T00:00:00", "uin": "74222", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent with Straight Flight Nevada Commercial Leasing LLC since October 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831226", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831225, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74221", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government is taking steps to monitor fraud under the Retail, Hospitality and Leisure business rate relief scheme, in the context of businesses falsely claiming a discount when they would otherwise be su", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831225", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831224, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74220", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much funding his Department is providing for the development of unmanned ground vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831224", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831223, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74219", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made on the development of unmanned ground vehicles for (a) logistics and (b) casualty evacuation.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831223", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831222, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74218", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made on the development of unmanned ground vehicles for engineering support.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831222", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831221, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74217", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made on the development of unmanned ground vehicles for combat support.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831221", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831220, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74216", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what comparative assessment he has made of the potential merits of (a) unmanned ground vehicles and (b) quadcopter drones.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831220", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831219, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74215", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to improve communications capabilities of flying drones.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831219", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831218, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74214", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to improve the communications capabilities of unmanned ground vehicles.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831218", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831217, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74213", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how his Department is increasing the integration of artificial intelligence into unmanned ground vehicles to counteract signal blocking.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831217", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831216, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74212", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how his Department is increasing the integration of artificial intelligence into flying drones to help counteract signal blocking.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831216", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831215, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74211", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2025 to Question 37808 on Prime Minister: Recruitment, if he will list the job title of each position in the Prime Minister\u2019s Office that was filled by exception since 4 July 2", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831215", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831214, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74210", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the document entitled Statistical bulletin - Civil Service Statistics: 2025, published on 30 July 2025, for what reason the proportion of staff in his Department who have self-reported a disabi", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831214", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831213, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74209", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to p.382 of the document entitled Central Government Supply Estimates 2024-25, Main Supply Estimates, HC139, published on 17 July 2025, what policy area relates to the Cabinet Office\u2019s contingent ", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831213", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831212, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74208", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his Department's policy is on whether (a) trade union diversity networks are eligible for trade union facility time and (b) whether staff can claim both diversity network time and facility time.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831212", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831211, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74207", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will place in the Library copies of each HR Connect newsletter issued since 1 January 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831211", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831210, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74206", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the (a) Crown Commercial Service and (b) Government Communications Service has (i) a framework agreement for the procurement of social influencers and (ii) roster of preferred or recommended influencers.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831210", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831209, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74205", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his Department's planned timetable is for the publication of the seventh UK National Action Plan for Open Government; and what consultation his Department has undertaken in relation to the sixth UK National", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831209", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831208, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74204", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an estimate of the total cost of the Civil Service paybill in the (a) 2023-24 and (b) 2024-25 financial years.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831208", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831207, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74203", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information (a) his Department and (b) the Crown Commercial Service hold on the fee structures used by Bloom Procurement Services Ltd under the NEPRO3 framework; and what proportion of public contracts awar", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831207", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831206, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74202", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Government press release entitled Internship Scheme To Get More Working Class Students Into Civil Service, published on 1 August 2025, whether children of (a) House of Commons Ministers and", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Service: Unpaid Work", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831206", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831205, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74201", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2025 to Question 64049 on Alcoholic Drinks, what those international conventions are.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831205", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831204, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74200", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department plans to provide alternative financial support to communities in West Dorset constituency following reductions in Government funding for neighbourhood plan", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831204", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831203, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74199", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of reductions in Government funding for neighbourhood plans on rural communities in West Dorset constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831203", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831202, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74198", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has had discussions with the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs on biometric processing for students from Gaza seeking to take up scholarships in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831202", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831201, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74197", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many students from Gaza that were awarded UK scholarships in the 2024-25 academic year are unable to take up their places due to lack of access to biometric enrolment facilities.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831201", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831200, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74196", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to provide safe routes for students from Gaza who have secured UK scholarships but are currently unable to meet biometric requirements.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831200", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831199, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74195", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of granting biometric deferrals for students from Gaza who have been awarded UK scholarships but are unable to access biometric fa", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831199", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831198, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74194", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether funding is available to upgrade hospital helipads to enable night-time operation.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831198", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831197, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74193", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the difference is between per-patient spend in (a) each hospital, (b) the average per-patient spend of hospitals in the top quarter of efficiency and (c) the average per-patient spend of hospi", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831197", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831196, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74192", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the potential financial impact of aligning funding to the average per-patient spend of the top quarter most efficient hospitals on rural hospitals.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831196", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831195, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74191", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what comparative assessment he has made of the efficiency (a) rural and (b) urban hospitals; and how many hospitals in each of those categories are within the top quarter most efficient hospitals.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831195", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831194, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74190", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average per-patient spend is per hospital (a) in England and (b) within the top quarter of most efficient hospitals.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831194", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831193, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74189", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether his Department responded to the correspondence from the Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government of 6 August 2025 on the proposed Chinese Embassy.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831193", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831192, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74188", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what due diligence was undertaken for the appointment of the UK ambassador to the US.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831192", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831191, "askingMemberId": 5238, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74187", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how the (a) commissioning and (b) funding model for gambling harm treatment services is structured across England; and whether he plans to issue a Letter of Comfort to Providers.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831191", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831190, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74186", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reason his Department pays council tax on Ministerial residences which are deemed to be second homes.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831190", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831189, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74185", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much council tax was paid by his Department on the Deputy Prime Minister\u2019s flat in Admiralty House in each month since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831189", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831188, "askingMemberId": 5169, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74184", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Lords' Commissioners of the Treasury will next meet.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831188", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831187, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74183", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, how much of the \u00a3350 million Nations and Regions investment fund will be spent in Huntingdon constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831187", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831186, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74182", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, when he expects the Office for Investment to establish a new national investment partnership framework to help", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831186", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831185, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74181", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which elements of the Global Combat air programme are included within the scope of the Industrial Strategy partnership with the Japanese government agreed in March 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831185", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831184, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74180", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, what procurement reforms will his Department introduce to improve the process in order to secure government contracts.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831184", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831183, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74179", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, what progress he has made in developing the new business growth service.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831183", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831182, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74178", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, what his Department's approach is to placements within industry.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831182", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831181, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74177", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, what recent progress has he made in establishing a high-calibre concierge service in the office for investment", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831181", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831180, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74176", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of increasing support for the Oxford to Cambridge growth c", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831180", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831179, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74175", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, what steps has he taken to increase support for the Oxford to Cambridge growth corridor.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831179", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831178, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74174", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, how much of the \u00a3500 million Local Innovation Partnerships Fund will be spent in Huntingdon co", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831178", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831177, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74173", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, what recent progress he has made on reducing the administrative costs of regulation for businesses.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831177", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831176, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74172", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, what his planned timetable is for publishing further information on the funding of the Cambridge Growth Compan", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831176", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831175, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74171", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, which areas within Cambridgeshire fall within the scope of the Cambridge Growth Company.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831175", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831174, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74170", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, how much funding his Department plans to provide to the Cambridge Growth Company.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831174", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831173, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74169", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, what funding he has provided to the Cambridge x Manchester Innovation partnership.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831173", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831172, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74168", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, what progress he has made on creating the new British Industrial Competitiveness Scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831172", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831171, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74167", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many days were lost to sickness absence by civil servants in their Department (a) in total and (b) on average per employee between 5 July 2024 and 4 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831171", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831170, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74166", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many days were lost to sickness absence by civil servants in their Department (a) in total and (b) on average per employee between 5 July 2024 and 4 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831170", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831169, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74165", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many days were lost to sickness absence by civil servants in their Department (a) in total and (b) on average per employee between 5 July 2024 and 4 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831169", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831168, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74164", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many days were lost to sickness absence by civil servants in their Department (a) in total and (b) on average per employee between 5 July 2024 and 4 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831168", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831167, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74163", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many days were lost to sickness absence by civil servants in their Department (a) in total and (b) on average per employee between 5 July 2024 and 4 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831167", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831166, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74162", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many days were lost to sickness absence by civil servants in their Department (a) in total and (b) on average per employee between 5 July 2024 and 4 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831166", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831165, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74161", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, how many days were lost to sickness absence by civil servants in their Department (a) in total and (b) on average per employee between 5 July 2024 and 4 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831165", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831164, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74160", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many days were lost to sickness absence by civil servants in their Department (a) in total and (b) on average per employee between 5 July 2024 and 4 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831164", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831163, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74159", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many days were lost to sickness absence by civil servants in their Department (a) in total and (b) on average per employee between 5 July 2024 and 4 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831163", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831162, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74158", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, how many days were lost to sickness absence by civil servants in their Department (a) in total and (b) on average per employee between 5 July 2024 and 4 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831162", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831161, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74157", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, how many days were lost to sickness absence by civil servants in their Department (a) in total and (b) on average per employee between 5 July 2024 and 4 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831161", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831160, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74156", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many days were lost to sickness absence by civil servants in their Department (a) in total and (b) on average per employee between 5 July 2024 and 4 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831160", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831159, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74155", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, how many days were lost to sickness absence by civil servants in their Department (a) in total and (b) on average per employee between 5 July 2024 and 4 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831159", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831158, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74154", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many days were lost to sickness absence by civil servants in their Department (a) in total and (b) on average per employee between 5 July 2024 and 4 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831158", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831157, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74153", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many days were lost to sickness absence by civil servants in their Department (a) in total and (b) on average per employee between 5 July 2024 and 4 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831157", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831156, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74152", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many days were lost to sickness absence by civil servants in their Department (a) in total and (b) on average per employee between 5 July 2024 and 4 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831156", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831155, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74151", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the lead time is between purchasing and delivery for Advanced Medium-Range Air-to-Air Missile missiles.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831155", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831154, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74150", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of growth potential in defence-related industries in Huntingdon constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831154", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831153, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74149", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of launching a defence growth deal in Huntingdon constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831153", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831152, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74148", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made on launching new defence growth deals.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831152", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831151, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74147", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what was included within the air defence export deal with Poland.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831151", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831150, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74146", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any defence operational developments are eligible for fast-track planning as nationally important Crown Developments in Huntingdon constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831150", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831149, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74145", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the scope is of Project TELUM.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831149", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831148, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74144", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the United States Navy\u2019s Modular Autonomous Surface Craft programme on future (a) Royal Navy fleet operations and (b) US Navy interoperability.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831148", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831147, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74143", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the outcome was of the recent trial by HMS Trent of the Helicopter Visual Landing Aid System.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831147", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831146, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74142", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many days were lost to sickness absence by civil servants in their Department (a) in total and (b) on average per employee between 5 July 2024 and 4 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831146", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831145, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74141", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to recommendation 38 of the Strategic Defence Review: Making Britain Safer: secure at home, strong abroad, published on 2 June 2025, if he will list the (a)Governments and (b) private financial ins", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831145", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831144, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74140", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 78 of the Strategic Defence Review: Making Britain Safer: secure at home, strong abroad, published on 2 June 2025, whether he has consulted external sources on the new Defence Diplomacy Str", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831144", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831143, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74139", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if he will have discussions with the US Consulate General in Belfast on how (a) heritage and (b) community groups in Northern Ireland can commemorate the 250th anniversary of the USA.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831143", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831142, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74138", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will have discussions with representatives of Londonderry Port on its viability as a national maritime defence asset.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831142", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831141, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74137", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if he will have discussions with Invest Northern Ireland and the Minister for the Economy of Northern Ireland on inward investment opportunities following the golf Open Championship at Royal Portrush Gol", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831141", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831140, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74136", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which public sector organisations are required to ensure that 50 per cent of their catering consists of British produce.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831140", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831139, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74135", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent progress she has made in establishing defence technical excellence colleges.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831139", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831138, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74134", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the potential merits of revising how the high needs national funding formula is calculated.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831138", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831137, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74133", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how attendees at the College for National Security are selected.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831137", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831136, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74132", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the size was of the asylum application decision appeals backlog on 1 August 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831136", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831135, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74131", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the size was of the initial asylum application decision backlog on 1 August 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831135", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831134, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74130", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent progress she has made in establishing the jobs and careers service.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831134", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831133, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74129", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential implications for his policies of deepening (a) commercial and (b) other economic ties between Russia and North Korea.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831133", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831132, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74128", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many of the Government\u2019s new AI Growth Zones are in (a) Cambridgeshire and (b) the Huntingdon constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831132", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831131, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74127", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many of the investible sites due to be delivered via the Strategic Sites Accelerator are in the Huntingdon constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831131", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831130, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74126", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, how many investable sites have been brought forward through the Government\u2019s \u00a3600m Stra", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831130", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831129, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74125", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 May 2025 to Question 49543, how many of the houses reacquired by his Department in January 2025 from Annington Homes have been used to house Afghans brought to the UK via (a) the Afgh", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831129", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831128, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74124", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Afghans were brought to the UK via the Afghan Response Route in each month the scheme was open.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831128", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831127, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74123", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of enhancing machine-speed (a) processing, (b) exploitation and (c) dissemination in order to rapidly transform raw sensor data into actionable intelligence.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831127", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831126, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74122", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he has taken to develop the Defence industrial base in order to rapidly scale lower-value and highly attritable autonomous collaborative platforms.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831126", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831125, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74121", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Commonwealth service-leavers have paid for visa applications for dependents since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831125", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831124, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74120", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Commonwealth service-leavers who have served between four and six years have paid for a visa upon discharge since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831124", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831123, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74119", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs the Tempest Global Combat Air Programme will create.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831123", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831122, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74118", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the projected contribution of the Tempest Global Combat Air Programme to GDP.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831122", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831121, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74117", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the contribution of Typhoon jets to GDP.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831121", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831120, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74116", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what funding his Department provides to BAE Systems' Falconworks programme.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831120", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831119, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74115", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress the Royal Navy has made on developing the Common Anti-air Modular Missile.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831119", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831118, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74114", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress the Royal Navy has made on Sea Viper Evolution.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831118", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831117, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74113", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the scope is of Project RECODE.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831117", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831116, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74112", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made on developing the Royal Navy\u2019s Force Threat Evaluation and Weapon Assignment functionality enabled by Artificial Intelligence/Machine Learning.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831116", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831115, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74111", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made on the development of a Type 91 uncrewed arsenal ship/missile barge.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831115", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831114, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74110", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the scope is of Project CORVUS.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831114", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831113, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74109", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Royal Navy\u2019s Mine Hunting Capability Block 1 operational capability is.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831113", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831112, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74108", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress the Royal Navy has made on developing Maritime Integrated Air and Missile Defence and Strike capability.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831112", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831111, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74107", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 14 of the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, what growth spillover benefits he plans to unlock in Huntingdon constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831111", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831110, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74106", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much funding from the National Security and Strategic Investment Fund will go to companies in Huntingdon constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831110", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831109, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74105", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the UK\u2019s Modern Industrial Strategy, CP 1337, published on 23 June 2025, what progress he has made on re-establishing a nuclear fuel cycle for defence reactor fuel.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831109", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831108, "askingMemberId": 1409, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74104", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many employees of the National Employment Savings Trust will be paid more than \u00a3160,000 in the current financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831108", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831107, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74103", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress his Department has made on developing an open-architecture app based combat management system interoperable across (a) the Army, (b) the Royal Navy, (c) the RAF and (d) UK Space Command.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831107", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831106, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74102", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to ensure that patient data is seamlessly shared between the NHS in (a) England and (b) the devolved Administrations.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831106", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831105, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74101", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential (a) merits of virtual teachers in allowing pupils to (i) rewatch and (ii) relisten to lessons and (b) impact of those teachers on pupils with lower achievement rate", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831105", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831104, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74100", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many cyber attacks there have been on the UK in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831104", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831103, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74099", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to help tackle cannabis use on streets.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831103", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831102, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74098", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) arm\u2019s-length bodies, (b) Government Departments, (c) agencies and (d) public bodies (i) have been assessed as redundant and (ii) are being prioritised for (A) merging and (B) closure.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831102", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831101, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74097", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of excessive alcohol consumption on levels of prevalence of cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831101", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831100, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74096", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Class A drugs have been seized from organised crime in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831100", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831099, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74095", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve levels of early diagnoses of dementia.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831099", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831098, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74094", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to deport convicted violent foreign criminals.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831098", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831097, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74093", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many deaths there have been due to sepsis in the last 24 months.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831097", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831096, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74092", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of people working in the UK illegally after their visa has expired.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831096", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831095, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74091", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many women aged between (a) 50-60 and (b) 60-70 years olds have been diagnosed with bowel cancer in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831095", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831094, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74090", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many women under the age of 18 have been diagnosed with ADHD in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831094", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831093, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74089", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been prosecuted for unpeaceful protest in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831093", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831092, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74088", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of recent trends in levels of water pollution in England.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831092", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831091, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74087", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of using Functional Electrical Stimulation devices to support people with Parkinson's disease.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831091", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831090, "askingMemberId": 5341, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74086", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will consider adding cheerleading as an approved (a) sport and (b) activity which can be assessed for GCSE Physical Education qualifications.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831090", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1831089, "askingMemberId": 5341, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74085", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to her Department\u2019s press release entitled Statutory levy and online slot stake limits to be introduced to tackle gambling harm, published on 27 November 2024, what steps she is ta", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1831089", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830867, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74084", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the DVLA\u2019s updated vehicle registration guidance on the UK\u2019s (a) classic and (b) historic vehicle sector.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Vehicles: Registration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830867", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830866, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74083", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what data her Department holds on the demographics of people who have taken bus journeys which were eligible for the price far cap.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bus Services: Fares", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830866", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830865, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74082", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) weekly, (b) monthly, (c) annual bus journeys eligible for the price fare cap were taken in (i) England, (ii) Lancashire and (iii) Fylde between 1 January 2023 and 1 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bus Services: Fares", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830865", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830864, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74081", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department is taking steps to help ensure that funding provided for The Dome in Farrington will affect wider Lancashire.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cricket: Lancashire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830864", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830863, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74080", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what funding has been allocated to the new homes accelerator during the Spending Review period.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830863", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830862, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74079", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the new homes accelerator will prioritise (a) specific geographical areas and (b) types of housing need.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830862", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830861, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74078", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the objectives are of the new homes accelerator programme; and how success will be measured against those objectives.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830861", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830860, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74077", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of (a) veterinary certification guidance, (b) trade missions and (c) inclusion in mentorship schemes on Lancashire producers.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Exports: Lancashire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830860", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830859, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74076", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to help ensure that Lancashire cheesemakers can access the benefits of the new Sanitary and Phytosanitary (SPS) Agreement on equal terms with other UK artisan e", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cheese: Lancashire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830859", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830858, "askingMemberId": 5135, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74075", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to (a) address the funding disparity and (b) provide additional financial support for Pendleside Hospice in Burnley.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pendleside Hospice: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830858", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830857, "askingMemberId": 5341, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74074", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to support families of UK citizens murdered overseas.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830857", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830856, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74073", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to (a) monitor and (b) help control the spread of Culicoides midges, the vectors of bluetongue virus serotype 3, in high-risk areas.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bluetongue Virus: Disease Control", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830856", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830855, "askingMemberId": 5341, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74072", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to (a) support retention in the police in England and (b) increase the number of police officers in Aylesbury constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830855", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830854, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74071", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to respond to the outbreak of bluetongue virus serotype 3 (BTV-3) in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bluetongue Virus: Disease Control", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830854", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830853, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74070", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to prevent the spread of bluetongue BTV3 disease among animals in England.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830853", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830852, "askingMemberId": 5088, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74069", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many drivers with three or more driving-related convictions retained their driving licence in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830852", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830851, "askingMemberId": 5088, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74068", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has made an assessment of the correlation between drivers (a) who fail to produce (i) a driving licence, (ii) an MOT certificate and (iii) insurance certificate and (b) convicted of (A) dangerous dr", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830851", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830850, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74067", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 1 September 2025 to Question 69995 on Primates: Imports, how many macaques have been imported into the UK for scientific research since 5 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Primates: Imports", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830850", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830849, "askingMemberId": 5218, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74066", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether she plans to (a) alter the statute of limitations and (b) review time limits for claims for (i) brain injuries and (ii) other lifelong conditions resulting from (A) medical and (B) clinical negligence.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Negligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830849", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830848, "askingMemberId": 5102, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74065", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 8 April 2025 to Question 44154 on Family Proceedings, when she plans to publish her Department's review of the presumption of parental involvement.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Family Proceedings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830848", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830847, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74064", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's press release entitled UK-France treaty targeting illegal crossings comes into force, published on 7 August 2025, whether there is a minimum number of returns that w", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830847", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830846, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74063", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether he is taking steps to support (a) campesino, (b) Indigenous and (c) Afro-descendent communities facing (i) land dispossession and (ii) forced evictions in Honduras.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Honduras: Property Rights", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830846", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830845, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74062", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) asylum hotels, (b) houses in multiple occupation used to house asylum seekers, (c) other properties used to house asylum seekers and (d) asylum seekers there were in Pontefract, Castlefor", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830845", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830844, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74061", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate she has made of the age profile of local government officers eligible for redundancy following the implementation of local government reform (a) in Cambridgeshire a", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Redundancy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830844", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830843, "askingMemberId": 5088, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74060", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of drivers convicted of (a) dangerous driving and (b) careless driving offences in the last five years were repeat offenders.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830843", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830842, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74059", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many full-time equivalent staff are working on responding to the Managing Pavement Parking consultation.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parking: Pedestrian Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830842", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830841, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74058", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she plans to take to measure the impact of the Financial Inclusion Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Financial Services: Disadvantaged", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830841", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830840, "askingMemberId": 5081, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74057", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking to ensure that all aspects of the financial services sector are provided opportunities to contribute the delivery of the Financial Inclusion Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Financial Services: Disadvantaged", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830840", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830839, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74056", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average time taken is for GP practices to secure funding for expansion through ICBs; and how his Department plans to reduce that time.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "GP Surgeries: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830839", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830838, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74055", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions NHS England has had with ICBs on the number of GP surgery expansion applications awaiting capital funding.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "GP Surgeries: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830838", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830837, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74054", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that local decision-making by ICBs is in line with national strategic priorities for primary care infrastructure growth.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Primary Care: Integrated Care Boards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830837", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830836, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74053", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with ICBs on providing GP practices with (a) clearer and (b) more transparent criteria on the approval process for (i) surgery expansion and (ii) new builds.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "GP Surgeries: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830836", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830835, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74052", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has considered introducing a ring-fenced national funding stream to support the expansion of GP surgeries in (a) high-growth and (b) underserved areas.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830835", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830834, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74051", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for his polices of regional variances in GP surgery expansion approvals under the integrated care board-led funding mechanism.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830834", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830833, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74050", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how his Department is working with integrated care boards to help tackle potential barriers for GP partnerships when seeking funding for (a) new premises and (b) expansion under the capital funding", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "General Practitioners: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830833", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830832, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74049", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that the funding model administered by integrated care boards supports (a) long-term infrastructure planning for primary care and (b) the timely development of new", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Primary Care: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830832", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830831, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74048", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to review capital funding allocation processes for new GP premises, in the context of the potential impact of the integrated care board framework on such expansions.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "GP Surgeries: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830831", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830830, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74047", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to improve support for bereaved families during Fatal Accident Inquests.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coroners", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830830", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830829, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74046", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of resources allocated to Coroners' Courts for Fatal Accident Inquests.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coroners", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830829", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830828, "askingMemberId": 4765, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74045", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Afghan Relocations and Assistance Policy-eligible Afghans living in British High Commission-supported hotels in Islamabad have been deported to Afghanistan.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830828", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830827, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74044", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the time taken to commence Fatal Accident Inquests.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coroners", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830827", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830826, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74043", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she plans to publish a list of community-owned helipads currently closed to Coastguard Search and Rescue helicopters due to CAP1264 Version 3 compliance requirements.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rescue Services: Helicopters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830826", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830825, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74042", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions her Department has had with (a) NHS Scotland, (b) the Scottish Government and (c) helicopter operators on (i) establishing responsibility for the use of community-owned helipads for hospital pa", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rescue Services: Helicopters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830825", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830824, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74041", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time is for the conclusion of a Fatal Accident Inquest.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coroners", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830824", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830823, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74040", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Fatal Accident Inquests are in progress.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coroners", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830823", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830822, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74039", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of Coastguard Search and Rescue helicopters having to land at alternative, un-surveyed sites instead of community-owned helipads on the safety of (a) patient", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rescue Services: Helicopters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830822", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830821, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74038", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has spent money on social media influencers since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department of Health and Social Care: Social Media", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830821", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830820, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74037", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance her Department provides on the (a) accountability and (b) operational documentation required for third-party helipads to be used for hospital patient transfers by Coastguard Search and Rescue heli", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rescue Services: Helicopters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830820", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830819, "askingMemberId": 5218, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74036", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has considered including lipedema as a relevant condition for NHS prescription of (a) Mounjaro injections and (b) other weight loss treatments.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Obesity: Drugs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830819", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830818, "askingMemberId": 5362, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74035", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking with the (a) Civil Aviation Authority and (b) Maritime and Coastguard Agency to help enable community-owned helipads used for hospital patient transfers to (a) meet CAP1264 V", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Rescue Services: Helicopters", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830818", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830817, "askingMemberId": 5088, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74034", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions she has had with the DVLA on reducing the number of vehicles with no registered keeper on the roads.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830817", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830816, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74033", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of extending the job guarantee scheme for newly qualified nurses and midwives to include (a) occupational therapists, (b) physi", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Allied Health Professions: Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830816", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830815, "askingMemberId": 5088, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74032", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate she has made of the number and proportion of vehicles that have no registered keeper.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830815", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830814, "askingMemberId": 5111, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74031", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the current Integrated Care Board (ICB)-led funding model in supporting the expansion of GP surgeries in areas with rapidly growing populations.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "GP Surgeries: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830814", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830813, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74030", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she has had discussions with the Secretary of State for Justice on the potential impact of auditing car park operator records where recurring disputes over charges have b", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parking: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830813", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830812, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74029", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the policy paper entitled UK and Palestinian strategic cooperation: memorandum of understanding, published on 28 April 2025, whether he has made an assessme", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Palestinian Authority", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830812", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830811, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74028", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the policy paper entitled UK and Palestinian strategic cooperation: memorandum of understanding, published on 28 April 2025, what recent assessment he has m", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Palestinian Authority", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830811", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830810, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74027", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of instructing the DVLA to audit car park operator records in cases where a recurring pattern of disputes over charges has been identified.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parking: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830810", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830809, "askingMemberId": 5174, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74026", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the challenges faced by military families when applying for school places (a) during school holiday periods and (b) other times outside of the normal admissions cycle.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830809", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830808, "askingMemberId": 4765, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-09T00:00:00", "uin": "74025", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of ARAP eligible Afghans currently staying in British High Commission supported hotels in Islamabad.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830808", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830807, "askingMemberId": 4813, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74024", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if she could publish a breakdown of the Government's \u00a34.5 billion spend on the transition to electric vehicles by (a) scheme and (b) year.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830807", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830806, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74023", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of the use of recovered life jackets on investigations into people smuggling networks.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "People Smuggling: Buoyancy Aids", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830806", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830805, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74022", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of life jackets recovered from small boat crossings since 4 July 2024; and what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of their disposal.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: English Channel", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830805", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830804, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74021", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of the process for the (a) collection, (b) storage and (c) disposal of life jackets recovered from small boat crossings.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: English Channel", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830804", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830803, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74020", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what (a) financial and (b) legal support has been made available for local nature recovery strategies.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nature Conservation: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830803", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830802, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74019", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to support law enforcement agencies with the technical capability to (a) detect and (b) disrupt livestreamed child sexual abuse in real time.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children: Internet", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830802", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830801, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74018", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of support for community land projects.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Assets", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830801", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830800, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74017", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that people in the UK who pay to direct livestreamed sexual abuse of children overseas are (a) identified and (b) prosecuted.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children: Internet", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830800", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830799, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74016", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress she has made on tackling (a) livestreamed child abuse and (b) other online sexual exploitation and abuse of children.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offences against Children: Internet", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830799", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830798, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74015", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of defaulting to a claimant\u2019s self-declared age where no independent verification is available on the provision of effective (a) safegua", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Age Assurance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830798", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830797, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74014", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what safeguards are in place to ensure that recording an asylum claimant\u2019s self-declared age does not place adults at risk of being accommodated with children.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Age Assurance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830797", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830796, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74013", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times her Department has recorded an asylum claimant\u2019s self-declared age as their official age in circumstances where their age could not be independently verified since June 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Age Assurance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830796", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830795, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74012", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether trends in levels of age-dispute cases have increased or decreased since June 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Age Assurance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830795", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830794, "askingMemberId": 4608, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74011", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the planned scope is of the proposed ban on trophy hunting imports; and when he plans to publish a timetable for introducing that legislation.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Animal Products: Imports", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830794", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830793, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74010", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on what evidential basis reducing the number of (a) Dartmoor ponies and (b) other livestock will effectively control overgrazing on Dartmoor.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Livestock: Dartmoor", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830793", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830792, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74009", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of Extended Producer Responsibility fee structures on UK manufacturers\u2019 investment in sustainable fibre-based composite packaging in", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Packaging: Recycling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830792", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830791, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74008", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether new Sustainable Farming Incentives will take into account the potential impacts of grazing moorland on controlling monocultures.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Sustainable Farming Incentive", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830791", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830790, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74007", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether a CITES permit is required to move live coral from Great Britain to Northern Ireland.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coral: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830790", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830789, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74006", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether moving live coral from Great Britain to Northern Ireland requires (a) an export number, (b) an Export Health Certificate, (c) a Common Health Entry Document and (d) using TRACE", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coral: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830789", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830788, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74005", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to protect Dartmoor ponies.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Horses: Dartmoor", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830788", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830787, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74004", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance his Department provides on whether live coral should be moved between Great Britain and Northern Ireland through the Green or Red Lane.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Coral: Northern Ireland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830787", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830786, "askingMemberId": 5096, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74003", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress she has made on the development of a national youth strategy; what discussions she has had with youth sector organisations on its design; and how she plans to ensure that young peop", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830786", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830785, "askingMemberId": 4591, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "74002", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Hammersmith Bridge Taskforce next plans to meet.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hammersmith Bridge: Repairs and Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830785", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830784, "askingMemberId": 3935, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "74001", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what (a) proportion and (b) amount of Universal Credit expenditure was for adults with non-Common Travel Area immigration status in the latest period for which information is available.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830784", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830783, "askingMemberId": 5223, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "74000", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department plans to reform the role of the Traffic Commissioner function for Great Britain.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830783", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830782, "askingMemberId": 5223, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73999", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to prevent the sale of nicotine pouches designed to look like confectionary products.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830782", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830781, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73998", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what his policy is on investors state dispute settlement provisions with India.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830781", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830780, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73997", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the (a) mobility provisions and (b) Double Contributions Convention in the UK\u2013India trade deal on UK sectors facing skills shortages; and if he wi", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830780", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830779, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73996", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, if he will publish UK\u2013India (a) tariff schedules, (b) rules of origin annexes and (c) concordance tables for businesses.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830779", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830778, "askingMemberId": 3935, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73995", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of levels of annually managed expenditure savings due to planned increases in the proportion of face to face (a) PIP and (b) Work Capability Assessments in each of the next fi", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830778", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830777, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73994", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how long the scrutiny period for documents laid before Parliament for the UK-India trade deal will be.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830777", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830776, "askingMemberId": 4874, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73993", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, when he will lay before Parliament the (a) section 42 Agriculture Act 2020 report and (b) Trade and Agriculture Commission\u2019s advice for the UK\u2013India trade deal.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830776", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830775, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73992", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that supported housing demand is met.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Supported Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830775", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830774, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73991", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent progress her Department has made in tackling knife crime.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Knives: Crime", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830774", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830773, "askingMemberId": 221, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73990", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made in ensuring additional NHS appointments are made available to people in North East Somerset and Hanham constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: North East Somerset and Hanham", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830773", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830772, "askingMemberId": 5352, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73989", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of taking into account both parents\u2019 income in Child Maintenance Service calculations.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Children: Maintenance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830772", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830771, "askingMemberId": 5263, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73988", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of the planned vape tax increase on (a) cigarette consumption and (b) illicit tobacco sales.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electronic Cigarettes: Excise Duties", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830771", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830770, "askingMemberId": 4742, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73987", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the number of police forces.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Police", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830770", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830769, "askingMemberId": 5263, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73986", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of using biodigesters to convert waste materials into organic fertilisers.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fertilisers: Waste", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830769", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830768, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73985", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the remit of the child poverty taskforce includes examining the potential impact of the two-child benefit cap.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Poverty: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830768", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830767, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "73984", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of the potential impact of the two-child benefit cap on levels of child poverty.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830767", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830766, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73983", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, when he plans to publish the responses to the call for evidence on steel trade measures, which closed on 7 August 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830766", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830765, "askingMemberId": 5263, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73982", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps her Department is taking to protect vulnerable consumers from disproportionate online insurance price increases.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Insurance: Prices", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830765", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830764, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73981", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, when he plans to publish (a) the steel strategy and (b) the Government's response to the Plan for Steel consultation which closed on 31 March 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830764", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830763, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73980", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the Trade Remedies Authority\u2019s proposal to maintain anti-dumping measures on ceramic tableware and kitchenware from China until July 2029 on (a) r", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830763", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830762, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73979", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, when his Department plans to make a decision on the Trade Remedies Authority\u2019s recommendation on anti-dumping duty on bicycles and parts from China; and if he will publish the underlying evidence befor", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830762", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830761, "askingMemberId": 4107, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73978", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, when he plans to publish the (a) final Impact Assessment and (b) data tables for the UK\u2013India trade deal.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830761", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830760, "askingMemberId": 5263, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73977", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the (a) potential merits and the (b) feasibility of installing solar panels on government-owned (a) buildings and (b) land.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Solar Power", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830760", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830759, "askingMemberId": 5263, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73976", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the prevalence of speeding in rural areas in Hampshire; and what assessment she made of the potential impact of speeding on pedestrians and cyclists' usage of roads in rural area", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Speed Limits: Hampshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830759", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830758, "askingMemberId": 5263, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73975", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of heavy and large goods vehicles on (a) rural roads and (b) the surrounding natural environment.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Large Goods Vehicles: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830758", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830757, "askingMemberId": 5263, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73974", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of housebuilding targets on the availability of school places in North East Hampshire constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Schools", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830757", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830756, "askingMemberId": 5263, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73973", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps his Department is taking to provide support for communities that host (a) battery storage facilities and (b) other energy infrastructure.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Energy: Infrastructure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830756", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830755, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73972", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of limited trial site locations on the ability of motor neurone disease patients to participate in research; and what support his Department prov", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Neurone Disease: Clinical Trials", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830755", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830754, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73971", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to support MND Care Centres to participate in (a) research studies and (b) MND-SMART.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Neurone Disease: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830754", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830753, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73970", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding his Department has allocated to support the (a) development and (b) expansion of MND clinical trial infrastructure.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Neurone Disease: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830753", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830752, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73969", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much money attributed to the Single Intelligence Account was included in UK NATO qualifying defence expenditure in (a) 2022-23 and (b) 2023-24.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830752", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830751, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73968", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions his Department has had with (a) NHS England and (b) the National Institute for Health and Care Research on (i) expanding the number of recruiting sites for and (ii) including James", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Neurone Disease: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830751", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830750, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73967", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of regional variation in patient access to motor neurone disease clinical trials; and what steps he is taking to ensure equitable access across al", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Motor Neurone Disease: Research", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830750", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830749, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73966", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the letter from the Minister for Defence Procurement and Industry to the hon. Member for South Suffolk of 29 July 2025, how much of the stated NATO-qualifying expenditure will be spent on strate", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830749", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830748, "askingMemberId": 5263, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73965", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to tackle shortages of medications used to treat Parkinson\u2019s disease.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Parkinson\u2019s Disease: Drugs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830748", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830747, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73964", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the letter from the Minister for Defence Procurement and Industry to the hon. Member for South Suffolk of 29 July 2025, how much of the stated NATO-qualifying expenditure will be spent on hybrid", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830747", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830746, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73963", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the letter from the Minister for Defence Procurement and Industry to the hon. Member for South Suffolk of 29 July 2025, how much of the stated NATO-qualifying expenditure will be spent on suppor", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830746", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830745, "askingMemberId": 5263, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73962", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support newly qualified midwives in securing employment following the completion of their training placements.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Midwives: Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830745", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830744, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73961", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the letter from the Right Hon. Member for Liverpool Garston to the Hon. Member for South Suffolk dated 29 July 2025, how much of the stated NATO-qualifying expenditure will be spent on the susta", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830744", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830743, "askingMemberId": 4519, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73960", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the letter from the Right Hon. Member for Liverpool Garston to the Hon. Member for South Suffolk dated 29 July 2025, how much of the stated NATO-qualifying expenditure will be spent on the imple", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830743", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830742, "askingMemberId": 5340, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "73959", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether she has made an assessment of the potential impact of UK stamp duty on the level of share trading volumes in Metlen.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830742", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830741, "askingMemberId": 5340, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "73958", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, with reference to the policy paper entitled UK and Palestinian strategic cooperation: memorandum of understanding, published on 28 April 2025, what recent assessment he has m", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830741", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830740, "askingMemberId": 5070, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73957", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department has spent on (a) salaries and (b) other related costs for (i) offices and (ii) staff for Police and Crime Commissioners in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830740", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830739, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73956", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to improve the quality of (a) education, (b) skills and (c) work provision in prisons.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prisons: Education and Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830739", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830738, "askingMemberId": 415, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73955", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that bereaved parents have equal access to specialist psychological support following (a) pregnancy and (b) baby loss.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Infant Mortality: Bereavement Counselling", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830738", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830737, "askingMemberId": 5335, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73954", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to expand access to weight loss medications through the NHS.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Obesity: Drugs", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830737", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830736, "askingMemberId": 1506, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73953", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 1 September 2025 to Question 69778 on Hysteroscopy: Correspondence, whether he has had recent discussions with NHS Trusts on ensuring that letters sent in advance of a hys", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hysteroscopy: Correspondence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830736", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830735, "askingMemberId": 1506, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73952", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 1 September 2025 to Question 69778 on Hysteroscopy: Correspondence, whether his Department holds information on the number of women who were not sent a letter in advance o", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hysteroscopy: Correspondence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830735", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830734, "askingMemberId": 1506, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73951", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent progress he has made in helping to reduce sudden cardiac deaths in (a) children and (b) young adults.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Heart Diseases: Children and Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830734", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830733, "askingMemberId": 1506, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73950", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the feasibility of implementing swab tests for the detection of Arrhythmogenic cardiomyopathies in children with risk factors for those diseases.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Heart Diseases: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830733", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830732, "askingMemberId": 1506, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73949", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps she has taken to help reduce (a) wealth and (b) productivity inequalities in England.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Productivity and Wealth: Equality", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830732", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830731, "askingMemberId": 4647, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73948", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the SFIA rate card in Annex 5 of the signed Work Order for Project_7114, published on Contracts Finder on 9 July 2025, if he will (a) publish the underlying rate card and (b) disclose any mark-", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830731", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830730, "askingMemberId": 5247, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73947", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of cancelled surgeries (a) at the East Kent Hospitals University Foundation Trust and (b) in England as a result of increased humidity in op", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830730", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830729, "askingMemberId": 5247, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73946", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with local authorities in areas where the EU Entry/Exit System will come into force on 12 October 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830729", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830728, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73945", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the number of Accident and Emergency intake staff.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Accident and Emergency Departments: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830728", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830727, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73944", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if 10 Downing Street has spent money on social media influencers since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "10 Downing Street: Social Media", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830727", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830726, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73943", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has spent money on social media influencers since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Social Media", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830726", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830725, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73942", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has spent money on social media influencers since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Education: Social Media", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830725", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830724, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73941", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether his Department has spent money on social media influencers since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology: Social Media", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830724", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830723, "askingMemberId": 5225, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73940", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of (a) reopening or (b) replacing the Community Ownership Fund to support communities seeking to take local assets into", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Ownership Fund", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830723", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830722, "askingMemberId": 5225, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73939", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what proportion of the \u00a339 billion allocated for affordable housing delivery will be spent in rural areas; and whether her Department plans to ringfence funding to support the de", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Affordable Housing: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830722", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830721, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73938", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve the quality of maternity care.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Maternity Services: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830721", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830720, "askingMemberId": 5225, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73937", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to help tackle (a) delays, (b) administrative burdens and (c) the availability of approved contractors to improve the operation of the Disable", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disabled Facilities Grants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830720", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830719, "askingMemberId": 5225, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73936", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking to help support people in (a) physically and (b) emotionally demanding jobs who are unable to continue working in their current role into their late 60s.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Older Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830719", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830718, "askingMemberId": 5225, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73935", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps is she taking to support people in (a) physically and (b) emotionally demanding jobs who are unable to continue working in their current role into their late 60s.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Older Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830718", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830717, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73934", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to help ensure adequate external scrutiny of the Child Poverty Strategy.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Poverty: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830717", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830716, "askingMemberId": 5225, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73933", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to expedite decisions on access to new treatments for secondary breast cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Breast Cancer: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830716", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830715, "askingMemberId": 4861, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73932", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his planned timetable is for implementing the proposed reforms to the Bathing Water Regulations 2013.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830715", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830714, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73931", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the forthcoming National Cancer Plan for England will include targets to improve the timeliness of diagnosis of blood cancers.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Blood Cancer: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830714", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830713, "askingMemberId": 5164, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73930", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has considered developing an invasive American signal crayfish eradication strategy in (a) England and (b) Norfolk.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830713", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830712, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73929", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps their Department is taking to implement the guidance entitled The government\u2019s approach to rural proofing 2025, published on 15 May 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Transport: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830712", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830711, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73928", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps their Department is taking to implement the guidance entitled The government\u2019s approach to rural proofing 2025, published on 15 May 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830711", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830710, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73927", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what steps their Department is taking to implement the guidance entitled The government\u2019s approach to rural proofing 2025, published on 15 May 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830710", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830709, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73926", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps their Department is taking to implement the guidance entitled The government\u2019s approach to rural proofing 2025, published on 15 May 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830709", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830708, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73925", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps their Department is taking to implement the guidance entitled The government\u2019s approach to rural proofing 2025, published on 15 May 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Business and Trade: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830708", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830707, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73924", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help increase the availability of treatments for Ehlers-Danlos syndrome in Cornwall.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830707", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830706, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73923", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps their Department is taking to implement the guidance entitled The government\u2019s approach to rural proofing 2025, published on 15 May 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830706", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830705, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73922", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps their Department is taking to implement the guidance entitled The government\u2019s approach to rural proofing 2025, published on 15 May 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Work and Pensions: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830705", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830704, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73921", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to help increase awareness of (a) Access to Work and (b) other employment support programmes.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment Schemes", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830704", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830703, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73920", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to integrate health and employment support for people with (a) arthritis and (b) other long-term health conditions.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment and Health: Chronic Illnesses", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830703", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830702, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73919", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 14 February 2025 to Question 28814 on Lead: Paint, whether his Department is taking steps to help tackle toxic lead paint in (a) homes and (b) public building", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lead: Paint", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830702", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830701, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73918", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 14 February 2025 to Question 28814 on Lead: Paint, if he will make it his policy to issue updated guidance.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Lead: Paint", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830701", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830700, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73917", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many incidents of animal welfare abuse have been recorded on intensive livestock farms in (a) England and (b) Norfolk in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Animal Welfare: Crime", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830700", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830699, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73916", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many vehicles were seized for waste crime offences in (a) South West Norfolk constituency and (b) Norfolk in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Waste: Crime", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830699", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830698, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73915", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to help tackle environmental harm in (a) South West Norfolk constituency and (b) Norfolk.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Environment Protection: Norfolk", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830698", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830697, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73914", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the financial impact of waste crime on (a) England, (b) Norfolk and (c) South West Norfolk constituency in the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Waste: Crime", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830697", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830696, "askingMemberId": 5338, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73913", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to help tackle waste crime.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Waste: Crime", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830696", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830695, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "73912", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to NHS England\u2019s publication entitled Interim commissioning guidance: Implementation of the NICE Technology Appraisal TA1026 and the NICE funding variation for tirzepatide (Mounjaro)", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830695", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830694, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73911", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to improve the process for moving geographical samples between Britain and the EU.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830694", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830693, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73910", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to facilitate the visa process for (a) non-British workers working for British companies within UK territorial waters and (b) British workers working in other countries\u2019 terri", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830693", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830692, "askingMemberId": 4616, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73909", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of changing the date for the award of the Wider Service Medal from 2018 to 2011.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Medals\r\n", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830692", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830691, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73908", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, why (a) notice or (b) a transition period was given for the closure of the ARAP scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Afghanistan: Refugees", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830691", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830690, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73907", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of a delay in settlement for British National (Overseas) child visa holders caused by a change from a 5+1 to a 10+1 route on access to (a) scholarships, (b) ", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Education: British National (Overseas)", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830690", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830689, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73906", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of extending the route to settlement from 5+1 to 10+1 years on the mental health of British (National) Overseas visa holders.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health: British National (Overseas)", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830689", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830688, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73905", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to allow British National (Overseas) visa holders to use the same border control queues as UK citizens at UK airports.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration Controls: British National (Overseas)", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830688", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830687, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73904", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to include voluntary work as a qualifying measure of societal contribution for British National (Overseas) visa holders under the proposed points-based pathway to Indefini", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration: British National (Overseas)", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830687", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830686, "askingMemberId": 5249, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73903", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to include traditional orchards in the list of irreplaceable habitats for biodiversity net gain.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Horticulture: Conservation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830686", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830685, "askingMemberId": 5031, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73902", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps she has taken to help reduce waiting lists for Approved Driving Instructor exams; and what recent progress her Department has made in reducing those backlogs.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830685", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830684, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73901", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of proposed changes to the BNO visa settlement route on older BNO visa holders\u2019 ability to access pension funds from Hong Kong.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pension Funds: British National (Overseas)", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830684", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830683, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73900", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking t support the expansion of (a) return to work and (b) accredited conversion courses at UK universities for (i) overseas workers and (ii) BNO visa holders seeking to re-enter ", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Employment Schemes: British National (Overseas) and Overseas Workers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830683", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830682, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73899", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, what assessment his Department has made of the potential impact of changes by technology companies to data protection features available in their products on consumers; and what steps h", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Data Protection: Consumers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830682", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830681, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73898", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what oversight mechanisms are in place to ensure that evidence submitted to the UK COVID-19 Inquiry from (a) bereaved families and (b) their legal representative is represented in (i) published mat", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Covid-19 Inquiry: Disclosure of Information", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830681", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830680, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73897", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will release all bereavement case studies submitted to Module 4 of the UK COVID-19 Inquiry in a timely manner.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Covid-19 Inquiry: Disclosure of Information", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830680", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830679, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73896", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of introducing monthly start dates for the 30 hours funded childcare scheme.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Childcare: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830679", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830678, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73895", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of (a) introducing penalties for certain uses of a mounted device while driving and (b) updating the guidance entitled Using a phone, sat na", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Road Traffic Offences: Mobile Phones", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830678", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830677, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73894", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria her Department uses to determine whether contracts for projects funded by the UK Government in Tunisia should be suspended due to alleged violations of human rights; and whether those cr", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Development Aid: Tunisia", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830677", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830676, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73893", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of increasing the repayment threshold of student loans on plan five in line with those on plan two.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Students: Loans", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830676", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830675, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73892", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of amending armed forces pension eligibility criteria to include personnel who served for more than six years but left the service before the age of 26 an", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830675", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830674, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73891", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, whether his Department plans to publish its legal advice on whether Israel is breaching international humanitarian law in Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: Israel", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830674", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830673, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73890", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2025 to Question 65451 on the School Support Staff Negotiating Body, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of establishing the body in shadow fo", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830673", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830672, "askingMemberId": 5336, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73889", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the UK Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism will have a military use exemption.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "UK Trade with EU: Carbon Emissions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830672", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830671, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73888", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking with farmers to help improve the resilience of domestic food supply chains.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food Supply", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830671", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830670, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73887", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of the availability of menopause support services.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Menopause: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830670", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830669, "askingMemberId": 5154, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73886", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the killing of civilians seeking aid in Gaza.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: Israel", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830669", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830668, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73885", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions her Department has held with the (a) Welsh and (b) Scottish governments on the potential impact of the establishment of School Support Staff Negotiating Body on (i) recruitment and (ii) retenti", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830668", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830667, "askingMemberId": 5234, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": true, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73884", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what (a) published and (b) unpublished research her Department has considered as part of its preparation for establishing the School Support Staff Negotiating Body; and what the titles are of each piece of rese", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830667", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830666, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73883", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has had recent discussions with her counterpart in the Scottish government on the potential long-term impact of changes to PIP eligibility on (a) people in Scotland who are in receipt of Adu", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Personal Independence Payment: Scotland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830666", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830665, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73882", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether people in Scotland who transition from Employment Support Allowance to Universal Credit will be (a) considered as new claimants and (b) subject to the new rules under the Universal Credit and Pe", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Universal Credit: Scotland", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830665", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830664, "askingMemberId": 5110, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73881", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether existing claimants of the Universal Credit health element will be considered as new claimants upon (a) periodic reassessment and (b) subsequent (i) appeal and (ii) reapplication.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Universal Credit", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830664", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830663, "askingMemberId": 5322, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73880", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of changes to the level of landfill tax on (a) housebuilding costs, (b) housing affordability and (c) the delivery of new homes.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Landfill Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830663", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830662, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73879", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he had with the Royal Norwegian Navy before it announced its decision to procure 5 Type 26 frigates from the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Type 26 Frigates: Norway", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830662", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830661, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73878", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will make an assessment of the potential impact of the Royal Norwegian Navy's decision to procure 5 Type 26 frigates from the UK on Scotland's economy.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Type 26 Frigates: Norway", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830661", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830660, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73877", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of increasing the level of compensation available to service personnel who develop mesothelioma as a result of exposure to asbestos.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Asbestos", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830660", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830659, "askingMemberId": 5279, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73876", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of increasing the level of compensation for service personnel who develop lung cancer and other asbestos-related diseases as a result of exposure to asbestos ", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Armed Forces: Asbestos", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830659", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830658, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "73875", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many lower-layer super output areas are within Telford constituency; how those areas are ranked by top (a) 1%, (b) 5% and (c) 10% in the index of multiple deprivation; and what impact that data has ", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830658", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830657, "askingMemberId": 5041, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "73874", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many lower-layer super output areas are within Telford constituency; how those areas are ranked by top (a) 1%, (b) 5% and (c) 10% in the index of multiple deprivation; and what impact that data ha", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830657", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830656, "askingMemberId": 5157, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73873", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to support Palestinian students in Gaza who have been offered places at UK universities to (a) complete visa biometric enrolment requirements, (b) travel safely to ", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Overseas Students: Gaza", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830656", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830655, "askingMemberId": 4521, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73872", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of retrospectively removing deductions of saved living costs from miscarriage of justice compensation awards made before August 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830655", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830654, "askingMemberId": 5177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73871", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will undertake a review of the impact of changes implemented as part of the Pensions Act 2014 on the ability of widows to inherit a spouse's state pension entitlement.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830654", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830653, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73870", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has considered the potential merits of extending the period for additional claims on the War Pension Scheme to six months.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "War Pensions", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830653", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830652, "askingMemberId": 4805, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73869", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has considered the potential merits of extending the access to work scheme to fund train tickets.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Access to Work Programme", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830652", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830651, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73868", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what information his Department holds on the (a) number and (b) type of (i) heat pump and (ii) boiler unit sold by each obligated boiler manufacturer, in the context of the Clean Heat Market ", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Boilers and Heat Pumps: Sales", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830651", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830650, "askingMemberId": 5359, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73867", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what her planned timetable is for publishing the outcome of the Arts Council England review.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Independent Review of Arts Council England", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830650", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830649, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73866", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what is the the cost of the RAF's surveillance flights over Gaza, for each month from October 2023 .", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830649", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830647, "askingMemberId": 4824, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73865", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what is the cost of using RAF (a) personnel and (b) equipment to prepare Straight Flight Nevada Commercial Leasing LLC for surveillance flights over Gaza, for each month from October 2023.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830647", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830646, "askingMemberId": 5177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73864", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of reducing the Housing Benefit taper rate from 65 per cent to 55 per cent.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830646", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830645, "askingMemberId": 5177, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73863", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of increasing the Housing Benefit earnings disregard from \u00a35 to \u00a357.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830645", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830644, "askingMemberId": 5085, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73862", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will provide funding to the National Vehicle Crime Intelligence Service in the Autumn Budget 2025 to enable it to expand its operations in key hotspots.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830644", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830643, "askingMemberId": 5314, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73861", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to her oral evidence to the House of Lords Economic Affairs Committee on 22 July 2025, on what evidential basis the country has cared more about bats than about commuter times for people in Leeds and ", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "High Speed 2 Line: West Yorkshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830643", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830642, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73860", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many additional driving tests have been provided in Lincolnshire since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Tests: Lincolnshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830642", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830641, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73859", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to tackle human health risks associated with spot on pet treatments containing (a) fipronil and (b) imidacloprid.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pets: Disease Control", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830641", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830640, "askingMemberId": 4126, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73858", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2025 to Question 62460 on Chronic Fatigue Syndrome: Health Services, whether a date has been set for the showcase event for post-acute infection conditions.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Chronic Fatigue Syndrome: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830640", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830639, "askingMemberId": 4608, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73857", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many driving test examiners have been employed by the DVSA in each month since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Tests", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830639", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830638, "askingMemberId": 4126, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73856", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure equitable (a) access to long covid services, (b) care outcomes and (c) patient experience for people with long covid.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Long Covid: Health Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830638", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830637, "askingMemberId": 4787, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73855", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department\u2019s Spending Review settlement includes funding for a multi-year extension to the Holiday activities and food programme.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Holiday Activities and Food Programme: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830637", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830636, "askingMemberId": 4608, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73854", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the measures the DVSA implemented to help reduce waiting times for driving tests that she announced to the Transport Select Committee on 23 April 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Tests: Waiting Lists", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830636", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830635, "askingMemberId": 4608, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73853", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment she has made of the potential impact of waiting times for driving tests on people seeking a driving licence.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Tests: Waiting Lists", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830635", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830634, "askingMemberId": 4608, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73852", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps she is taking to reduce the length of waiting times for driving tests.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Tests: Waiting Lists", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830634", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830633, "askingMemberId": 4608, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73851", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average waiting time is for driving tests at (a) Hawick, (b) Galashiels, (c) Kelso, (d) Duns and (e) Berwick-On-Tweed test centres.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Tests: Scottish Borders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830633", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830632, "askingMemberId": 4647, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73850", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will itemise each (a) contract awarded and (b) payment made to Public Digital by his Department since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830632", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830631, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73849", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential (a) financial and (b) other impacts of the proposed strike action on 10 September 2025 on the horseracing industry.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830631", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830630, "askingMemberId": 5348, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73848", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps her Department is taking to tackle number plate cloning; and what assessment she has made of the potential impact of vehicle cloning on (a) the finances, (b) the legal position and (c) other factors ", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Vehicle Number Plates: Fraud", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830630", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830629, "askingMemberId": 5267, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73847", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of (a) trends in levels of (i) flooding and (ii) resulting closure of the B478 from Sonning to Playhatch and (b) the potential impact of climate change on f", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830629", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830628, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73846", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of HMS Richmond's planned use of the Taiwan Strait in September on UK relations with China.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830628", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830627, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73845", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to her Department's press release entitled Criminals to face football, travel, club and pub bans, published on 23 August 2025, which prisons are the 2,400 new prison places since July 2024 located ", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prison Accommodation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830627", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830626, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73844", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department has spent money on social media influencers since July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport: Social Media", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830626", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830625, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73843", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to increase levels of funding available for farmers.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Farmers: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830625", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830624, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73842", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to support food security.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food Supply", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830624", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830623, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73841", "questionText": "To ask the Solicitor General, what steps she is taking to help ensure the effective prosecution of rural crime.", "answeringBodyId": 88, "answeringBodyName": "Attorney General", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Crime: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830623", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830622, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73840", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking with the Secretary of State for the Home Department to tackle violence against women and girls.", "answeringBodyId": 31, "answeringBodyName": "Women and Equalities", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gender Based Violence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830622", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830621, "askingMemberId": 5252, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73839", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of including pet treatments as a significant source of pesticides as part of the UK Pesticides National Action Plan 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pesticides", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830621", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830620, "askingMemberId": 5294, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73838", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were employed by her Department at the rank of Chief Immigration Officer at the end of the 2015-16 financial year.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration Officers", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830620", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830619, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73837", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether his Department has investigated the causes of fires at electrical substations in the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Electrical Substations: Fires", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830619", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830618, "askingMemberId": 5350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73836", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that cancer early diagnosis targets are appropriate for blood cancers.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cancer: Diagnosis", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830618", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830617, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73835", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much the Pensions Regulator has spent on equipment to enable staff to work from home in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pensions Regulator: Remote Working", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830617", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830616, "askingMemberId": 350, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73834", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much the National Employment Savings Trust has spent on equipment to enable staff to work from home in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "National Employment Savings Trust Corporation: Remote Working", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830616", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830615, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73833", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has issued guidance to special advisers on undertaking (a) national and (b) local political activities during working hours when accompanying Ministers in a local election purdah period.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Special Advisers: Elections", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830615", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830613, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73831", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has provided guidance on whether Ministerial meetings arranged through the Labour Infrastructure Forum should be declared in Ministerial transparency returns.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Labour Infrastructure Forum: Meetings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830613", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830612, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73830", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2025 to Question 68481 on 10 Downing Street: ICT, whether Number 10 has its own operational Bloomberg terminal, independent from the Treasury ones.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "10 Downing Street: ICT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830612", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830611, "askingMemberId": 4474, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73829", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 12 June 2025 to Question 54875 on Admiralty House: Council Tax, whether Council Tax (a) discount, exemption, disregard and (b) premium is applied to the Government's bill for each of th", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Admiralty House: Council Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830611", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830610, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73828", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of the demonstrators arrested in central London on 9 August 2025 were (a) arrested for supporting Palestine Action and (b) subsequently charged for the same offence.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830610", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830609, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73827", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of building a bypass on the A1 at Buckden roundabout, in the context of potential levels of traffic caused by (a) Universal Studios, (b) proposed devel", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "A1: Cambridgeshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830609", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830608, "askingMemberId": 5171, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73826", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help improve the provision of healthy food options in hospital vending machines.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospitals: Vending Machines", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830608", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830607, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73825", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with his US counterpart on the (a) purpose and (b) efficacy of the AUKUS programme.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "AUKUS", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830607", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830606, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73824", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the quality of the treatment available to people with Leukaemia in (a) Newcastle-under-Lyme constituency and (b) Staffordshire.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Leukaemia: Staffordshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830606", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830605, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73823", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of her Department's suppliers for (a) ICT (b) stationery and (c) office furniture are (i) supplied by UK businesses and (ii) manufactured in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Work and Pensions: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830605", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830604, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73822", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to encourage the procurement of British-made office products and stationery by (a) her Department and (b) its arms-length bodies.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Work and Pensions: Stationery", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830604", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830603, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73821", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, from which countries her Department has sourced (a) pulp and (b) finished paper for (i) official stationery and (ii) other printed materials.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Work and Pensions: Paper", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830603", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830602, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73820", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what proportion of her Department\u2019s suppliers for (a) ICT (b) stationery and (c) office furniture are (i) supplied by UK businesses and (ii) manufactured in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Treasury: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830602", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830601, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73819", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps her Department is taking to to encourage the procurement of British-made office products and stationery by (a) her Department and (b) its arms-length bodies.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Treasury: Stationery", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830601", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830600, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73818", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, from which countries her Department has sourced (a) pulp and (b) finished paper for (i) official stationery and (ii) other printed materials.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Treasury: Paper", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830600", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830599, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73817", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, from which countries the Prime Minister sources (a) pulp and (b) finished paper for (i) official stationery and (ii) other printed materials.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prime Minister: Paper", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830599", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830598, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73816", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of her Department\u2019s (a) ICT (b) stationery and (c) office furniture suppliers are (i) supplied by UK businesses and (ii) manufactured in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Justice: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830598", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830597, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73815", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to encourage the procurement of British-made office products and stationery by (a) her Department and (b) its arms-length bodies.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Justice: Stationery", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830597", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830596, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73814", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, from which countries her Department has sourced (a) pulp and (b) finished paper for (i) official stationery and (ii) other printed materials.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Justice: Paper", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830596", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830595, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73813", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, how many an what proportion of his Department\u2019s (a) ICT (b) stationery and (c) office furniture suppliers are (i) supplied by UK businesses and (ii) manufactured in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Business and Trade: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830595", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830594, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73812", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what steps his Department has taken to encourage the procurement of British-made office products and stationery by (a) his Department and (b) its arms-length bodies.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Business and Trade: Stationery", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830594", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830593, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73811", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, from which countries his Department has sourced (a) pulp and (b) finished paper for (i) official stationery and (ii) other printed materials.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Business and Trade: Paper", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830593", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830592, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73810", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of her Department\u2019s (a) ICT (b) stationery and (c) office furniture suppliers are (i) supplied by UK businesses and (ii) manufactured in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Office: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830592", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830591, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73809", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to encourage the procurement of British-made office products and stationery by (a) the Department and (b) its arms-length bodies.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Office: Stationery", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830591", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830590, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73808", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, from which countries her Department has sourced (a) pulp and (b) finished paper for (i) official stationery and (ii) other printed materials.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Office: Paper", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830590", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830589, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73807", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of his Department's (a) ICT (b) stationery and (c) office furniture suppliers are (i) supplied by UK businesses and (ii) manufactured in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Defence: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830589", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830588, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73806", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the procurement of British-made office products and stationery by (a) his Department and (b) its arms-length bodies.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Defence: Stationery", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830588", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830587, "askingMemberId": 5285, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73805", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, from which countries his Department has sourced (a) pulp and (b) finished paper for (i) official stationery and (ii) other printed materials.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Defence: Paper", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830587", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830586, "askingMemberId": 5212, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73804", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many children injured in Gaza as a result of the conflict have been brought to the UK for medical treatment; and what steps he is taking to support other Palestinian children who may benefit fr", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Gaza: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830586", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830585, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73803", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average age was of people recorded as having entered the U.K. illegally in the most recent period for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: Age", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830585", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830584, "askingMemberId": 5356, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "73802", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of those who are recorded as having entered the U.K. illegally were (a) women and (b) men in the most recent period for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830584", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830583, "askingMemberId": 5034, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-08T00:00:00", "uin": "73801", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department has engaged the Sport, Leisure and Culture Consultancy (SLC) as an external provider.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830583", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830582, "askingMemberId": 5275, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73800", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the waiting list for a car driving test was at the DVLA test centre in Dunfermline for each of the last 12 months.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Tests: Dunfermline", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830582", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830581, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73799", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the National Infrastructure and Service Transformation Authority's Annual Report 2024\u201325, published on 11 August 2025, for what reason no evaluation was complet", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Grenfell Tower", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830581", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830580, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73798", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department has (a) commissioned or (b) procured third-party providers to (i) assess, (ii) index or (iii) identify (A) extremism and (B) disinformation.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disinformation and Radicalism", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830580", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830579, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73797", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 28 July 2025 to Question 69054 on Community Cohesion and Resilience Programme: Finance, for what policy reason the funding for the Community Cohesion an", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Cohesion and Resilience Programme: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830579", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830578, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73796", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 10 April 2025 to Question HL6508 Road Signs and Markings, what is the evidential basis for there being no need for (a) regulations or (b) new guidance.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Road Signs and Markings", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830578", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830577, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73795", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much was spent on the Affordable Housing Programme (a) 2015-2018 and (b) (2016-2021) in each year of operation; and how much has (i) been spent and (b) is forecast to be spen", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Affordable Housing: Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830577", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830576, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73794", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 28 July 2025 to Question 65978 on Islamophobia, whether the True Vision reporting portal will use the Government's definition of Islamophobia.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Islamophobia", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830576", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830575, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73793", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what consideration she has made of introducing a council tax referendum threshold for town and parish councils with precepts above \u00a3100 on Band D.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Council Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830575", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830574, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73792", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she plans to amend (a) planning policy and (b) permitted development rights in relation to asylum accommodation.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830574", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830573, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73791", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, whether he has had recent discussions with (a) Lightspeed and (b) other (i) broadband and (ii) connectivity companies on the effectiveness of their consultation processes with local res", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Telecommunications: Infrastructure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830573", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830572, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73790", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent reports his Department has received on the (a) political and (b) security situation in the United Republic of Tanzania.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Tanzania: Politics and Government", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830572", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830571, "askingMemberId": 5168, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73789", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of the Government issuing an official apology to people affected by forced adoptions.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Adoption", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830571", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830570, "askingMemberId": 4592, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73788", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to provide an answer to the freedom of information request with reference FOI2025/17106.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830570", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830569, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73787", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment her Department has made of the potential impact of open access rail operators on (a) connectivity, (b) passenger choice and (c) service quality.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Railways", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830569", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830568, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73786", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an estimate of the potential cost to (a) the public purse and (b) private developers of constructing 12 new towns.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "New Towns: Construction", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830568", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830567, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73785", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to help increase the number of qualified planners in local government.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Planning Authorities: Staff", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830567", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830566, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73784", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2025 to Question 26699 on Cambridgeshire and Peterborough Combined Authority, whether she plans to bring forward legislative proposals to all", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Government: Reorganisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830566", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830565, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73783", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her proposals for English devolution could require the further re-organisation of (a) NHS Bedfordshire, Luton and Milton Keynes Integrated Care Board and (b) other integr", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Integrated Care Boards: Reorganisation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830565", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830564, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73782", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who breached the terms of their visa were subsequently granted indefinite leave to remain since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Immigration", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830564", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830563, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73781", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of the level of funding for Bedfordshire Fire and Rescue Service.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Bedfordshire and Luton Fire and Rescue Service: Finance", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830563", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830562, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73780", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with her French counterpart on intercepting small boats in shallow waters.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Undocumented Migrants: English Channel", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830562", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830561, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73779", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an estimate of the number and proportion of medical students who graduated at the end of the 2024-25 academic year who will begin work in the NHS in the 2025-26 academic year.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Graduates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830561", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830560, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73778", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of medical students who graduated in each of the past five years were working in the NHS on 1 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Graduates", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830560", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830559, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73777", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many medical students started university in each of the past five years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Medicine: Higher Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830559", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830558, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73776", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an estimate of the number of medical students starting university in autumn 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Medicine: Higher Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830558", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830557, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73775", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to help improve access to life-extending (a) treatments and (b) medicines for patients with incurable secondary breast cancer in Mid Bedfordshire constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Breast Cancer: Mid Bedfordshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830557", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830556, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73774", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of his Department's funding for children\u2019s hospices.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospices: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830556", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830555, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73773", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to improve access to NHS Continuing Healthcare for people with (a) Progressive Supranuclear Palsy and (b) Corticobasal Degeneration in Mid-Bedforshire constituency.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Neurological Diseases: Mid Bedfordshire", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830555", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830554, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73772", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether access to dementia specialist nurses will be available through his Department's planned Neighbourhood Health Services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Nurses: Dementia", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830554", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830553, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73771", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the press release entitled Managing healthcare easy as online banking with revamped NHS App, published on 3 July 2025, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people wh", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "NHS: Software", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830553", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830552, "askingMemberId": 5100, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73770", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the press release entitled PM launches new era for NHS with easier care in neighbourhoods, published on 2 July 2025, how his Department plans to define neighbourhoods in rural are", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Community Care: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830552", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830551, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73769", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of ongoing contracts for the provision of migrant hotel services were awarded through (a) competitive tender, (b) direct award and (c) emergency procurement.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Asylum: Hotels", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830551", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830550, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73768", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department holds information on any (a) complaints and (b) concerns received from people housed in migrant hotels on the (i) conduct and (ii) quality of services provided by (A) private co", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830550", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830549, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73767", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on (a) employment conditions, (b) levels of pay and (c) training undertaken by staff working for subcontractors in migrant hotels.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830549", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830548, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73766", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department requires contractors providing hotel accommodation to asylum seekers to disclose their use of subcontractors.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830548", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830547, "askingMemberId": 5072, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73765", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which companies held contracts for the provision of hotel accommodation for asylum seekers on 1 September 2025; and what the (a) value and (b) duration is for each of those contracts.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830547", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830546, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73764", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information her Department holds on (a) the number of and (b) which local authorities had Local Development Orders in force on 1 September 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Local Development Orders", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830546", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830545, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73763", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2025 to Question 31485 on Planning Permission, what criteria her Department uses to determine whether a planning application for non-governm", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Planning Permission", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830545", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830544, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73762", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate she has made of the potential impact of her Department's decision to end financial payments to local authorities for getting long-term empty homes back into use thr", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Empty Property", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830544", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830543, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73761", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the National Housing Bank will require the delivery of a specified number of (a) affordable and (b) social rent housing when agreeing loans for developers.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "National Housing Bank", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830543", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830542, "askingMemberId": 5354, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73760", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with relevant stakeholders on potential changes to legislation that would help increase the number of companies that are able to donate s", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Waste", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830542", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830541, "askingMemberId": 4366, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73759", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information her Department holds on the number of meetings between the Working Group on Anti-Muslim Hatred/Islamophobia Definition and (a) external organisations and (b) oth", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Anti-muslim Hatred/Islamophobia Definition Working Group", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830541", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830540, "askingMemberId": 5250, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73758", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of amending statutory guidance to improve access to social housing for survivors of domestic abuse with debt living in temp", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Domestic Abuse: Social Rented Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830540", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830539, "askingMemberId": 5250, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73757", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department is taking steps to help prevent victims of financial abuse being barred from bidding on social housing when in temporary accommodation because of debt accr", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Domestic Abuse: Social Rented Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830539", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830538, "askingMemberId": 5354, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73756", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the child poverty strategy will look beyond the 10-year timeframe.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Poverty: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830538", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830537, "askingMemberId": 5250, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73755", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information her Department holds on the number of families that have been living in emergency accommodation for longer than the six-week legal limit.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Temporary Accommodation: Families", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830537", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830536, "askingMemberId": 5250, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73754", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department has put in place a process to track the distance that families have moved when placed in temporary accommodation out of their local authority area.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Temporary Accommodation: Families", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830536", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830535, "askingMemberId": 5250, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73753", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the age breakdown is of children over the age of ten in temporary accommodation; and what steps she is taking to help ensure that the accommodation is suitable for children.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Temporary Accommodation: Children", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830535", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830534, "askingMemberId": 5250, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73752", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of families in temporary accommodation were placed outside their own local authority area in the latest period for which data is available.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Temporary Accommodation: Families", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830534", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830532, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73750", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the potential impact of his policies on the ability of farmers to diversify their income streams to support their farming business.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Farmers: Income", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830532", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830531, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73749", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he has had recent discussions with (a) representatives of rural communities and (b) third party bodies on including the energy needs of off grid communities within the Warm Homes Plan", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Warm Homes Plan: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830531", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830530, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73748", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he has had recent discussions with (a) representatives of rural communities and (b) third party bodies on including the energy needs of canal boat owning communities within the Warm H", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Warm Homes Plan: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830530", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830529, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73747", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, whether he has had recent discussions with (a) representatives of rural communities and (b) third party bodies on including the energy needs of rural communities within the Warm Homes Plan.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Warm Homes Plan: Rural Areas", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830529", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830528, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73746", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has had recent discussions with the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government on (a) assessing the adequacy and (b) improving the availability of single occupancy for veterans.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterans: Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830528", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830527, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73745", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to publish the next report by Alma Economics on the evaluation of the Op FORTITUDE and Reducing Veterans Homelessness programme.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Veterans: Homelessness", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830527", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830526, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73744", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when Ministers in her Department last met representatives of the independent school sector to discuss issues facing that sector.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Private Education", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830526", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830525, "askingMemberId": 4781, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73743", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of clause 8 of the Crime and Policing Bill on the number of police interceptions of (a) pedal bikes and (b) e-bikes whose riders are committing ant", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Anti-social Behaviour: Bicycles", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830525", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830524, "askingMemberId": 4869, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73742", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, if he will place restrictions on the trade of British-manufactured equipment with Israel in circumstances where there is evidence of a risk that such equipment will be used t", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830524", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830523, "askingMemberId": 4403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73741", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions she has had with (a) the Scottish Government and (b) local authorities on providing support to help tackle reinforced autoclaved aerated concrete in residential ", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Concrete", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830523", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830522, "askingMemberId": 4403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73740", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of reinforced autoclaved aerated concrete in residential buildings on (a) homeowners and (b) tenants.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Concrete", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830522", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830521, "askingMemberId": 4403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73739", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions she has had with insurance providers to homeowners impacted by reinforced autoclaved aerated concrete.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Concrete", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830521", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830520, "askingMemberId": 4403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73738", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions she has had with mortgage providers to homeowners impacted by reinforced autoclaved aerated concrete.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Concrete", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830520", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830519, "askingMemberId": 4403, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73737", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps her Department is taking to help support owners of homes impacted by reinforced autoclaved aerated concrete which were sold by local authorities.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Concrete", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830519", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830518, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73736", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which companies have expressed an interest in investing in Public Private Partnerships.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Public Private Partnerships", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830518", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830517, "askingMemberId": 178, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73735", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will provide information on the (a) new Public Private Partnerships and (b) in what way they differ from Private Finance Initiatives.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Health Services: Private Finance Initiative and Public Private Partnerships", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830517", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830516, "askingMemberId": 5156, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73734", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to her Oral Statement of 30 June 2025 on Welfare Reform, if she will provide a breakdown by (a) location and (b) roles of the additional 6,700 mental health workers.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Mental Health Services: Recruitment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830516", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830515, "askingMemberId": 5184, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73733", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of exempting people with sickle-cell anaemia from prescription charges.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prescriptions: Fees and Charges", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830515", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830514, "askingMemberId": 5361, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73732", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has undertaken recent research on the potential merits of opening desalination plants to help ensure the resilience of the domestic water supply.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Housing: Water Supply", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830514", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830513, "askingMemberId": 4494, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73731", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people pay income tax at age (a) 16, (b) 17, (c) 18, (d) 19, (e) 20 and (f) 21.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Income Tax: Young People", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830513", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830512, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73730", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with which (a) external processors and (b) IT suppliers are (i) special category data and (ii) other personal data shared under the College for National Security Privacy Notice, published on 19 June 2025; and wh", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "College for National Security: Data Protection", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830512", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830511, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73729", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 1 April 2025 to Question 41254 on Ministers: Aviation, how much his Department has spend on carbon offsetting under the RM6251 Energy Supply Framework since July 2024; and how many tonn", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministers: Aviation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830511", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830510, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73728", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 1 April 2025 to Question 40584 on 9 Downing Street: Media, if he will publish the (a) social value outcomes reports and (b) diversity reports from the last four quarters.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: OCS Group", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830510", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830509, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73727", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 1 April 2025 to Question 40919 on Civil Servants: Personnel Management, if he will publish the Mutually Agreed Exits guidance.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Servants: Personnel Management", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830509", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830508, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73726", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's guidance entitled Public Bodies Handbook \u2013 Part 2: The Approvals Process for the Creation of New Arm\u2019s-Length Bodies, whether his Department's public bodies team assessed Passe", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Passenger Standards Authority", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830508", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830507, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73725", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 11 July 2025, to Question 64828, on Central Government: Empty Property, if he will list the datasets that (a) were previously held on the Electronic Property Information Mapping Service", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Central Government: Empty Property", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830507", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830506, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73724", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reason the Civil Service Board has ceased operation; and whether its functions have been taken over by (a) a new or (b) pre-existing body.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Civil Service Board", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830506", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830505, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73723", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the policy paper entitled Profile: GRU cyber and hybrid threat operations, published on 18 July 2025, whether the GRU has (a) engaged with and (b) targeted UK (i) trade unions, (ii) political p", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cybercrime: Russia", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830505", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830504, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73722", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 1 April 2025 to Question 41254 on Ministers: Aviation, whether (a) his Department and (b) the Crown Commercial Service hold information on the (i) locations and (ii) activities undertak", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministers: Aviation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830504", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830503, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73721", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will undertake a public consultation on the proposed duty of candour.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Public Sector: Accountability", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830503", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830502, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73720", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish FOI reference, FOI2025/09624, dated 16 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Freedom of Information", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830502", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830501, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73719", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Answer of 31 July 2025 to Question HL9824 on Government Departments: Public Lavatories, when that guidance was last updated.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Government Departments: Public Lavatories", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830501", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830500, "askingMemberId": 4384, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73718", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has made payments to Inter Mediate since 4 July 2024.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Inter Mediate", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830500", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830499, "askingMemberId": 5047, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73717", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of including hazard perception tests for drivers who have been diagnosed with glaucoma.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Driving Tests: Glaucoma", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830499", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830498, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73716", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether she will make an assessment of the potential merits of automatic planning permission for extending helipad operation hours at major trauma hospitals.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Air Ambulance Services: Planning Permission", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830498", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830497, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73715", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing legislative safeguards to protect existing hospital helipads from closure.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Air Ambulance Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830497", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830496, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73714", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help ensure that existing hospital helipads are protected from (a) planning and (b) operational restrictions.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Air Ambulance Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830496", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830495, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73713", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which hospitals are in the top quartile of most efficient hospitals.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospitals: Standards", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830495", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830494, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73712", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average per-patient spend is in (a) all hospitals and (b) the top quartile of efficient hospitals.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Hospitals: Expenditure", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830494", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830493, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73711", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how and what proportion of major trauma hospitals operate 24-hour hospital helipads in England.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Air Ambulance Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830493", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830492, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73710", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to support young disabled people into further (a) training and (b) education.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disability: Further Education and Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830492", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830491, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73709", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to help reduce inequalities for young disabled people in the labour market.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Disability: Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830491", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830490, "askingMemberId": 54, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-04T00:00:00", "uin": "73708", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if she will take steps with her international counterparts to include Commoners of the New Forest as a national minority according to the criteria for such a designation under th", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": true, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": null, "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830490", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830489, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73707", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to improve (a) awareness and (b) enforcement of legislation on air weapon (i) safety and (ii) responsible ownership.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Airguns", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830489", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830488, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73706", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to improve public (a) awareness and (b) education on the (i) dangers of misusing air weapons and (ii) impact of that misuse on (A) animals and (B) communities.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Airguns: Misuse", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830488", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830487, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73705", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has a budget for retraining programmes for adult workers transitioning from oil and gas to renewable energy.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Renewable Energy: Training", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830487", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830486, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73704", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what discussions his Department has had with employers in the oil and gas sector in England on (a) skills transition and (b) workforce retention.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offshore Industry: Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830486", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830485, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73703", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, for what reason the Oil and Gas Transition Training Fund is restricted to Scottish residents; and whether he plans to extend that scheme to workers in England.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Oil and Gas Transition Training Fund", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830485", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830484, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73702", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what (a) funding and (b) retraining support is available for oil and gas workers in England impacted by the transition to renewable energy.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offshore Industry: Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830484", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830483, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73701", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of net zero policies on employment in the oil and gas sector in England.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Offshore Industry: Employment", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830483", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830482, "askingMemberId": 4515, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73700", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions her Department has had with food and drink wholesalers on reforming the business rates system.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Food: Wholesale Trade", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830482", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830481, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73699", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will commission an independent review of the proposed changes to Inheritance Tax.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830481", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830480, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73698", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she plans to take to ensure transparency in the modelling of the proposed Inheritance Tax changes.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830480", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830479, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73697", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment she has made of the potential impact of proposed Inheritance Tax changes on family (a) businesses and (b) farms.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Agriculture and Business: Inheritance Tax", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830479", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830478, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73696", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate she has made of the loss of tax revenue from non-VAT registered companies with turnover above the VAT threshold in the next five years.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Companies: VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830478", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830477, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73695", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether her Department has made a recent assessment of the potential impact of lowering the VAT threshold on the economy.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "VAT", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830477", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830476, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73694", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to prioritise industrial rooftops over (a) arable farmland and (b) countryside fields for solar panel locations.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Countryside and Farms: Solar Power", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830476", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830475, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73693", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with stakeholders on ending farrowing crate usage for pigs.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pigs: Animal Housing", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830475", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830474, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73692", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, for what purposes their Department has used artificial intelligence in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 28, "answeringBodyName": "Wales Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Wales Office: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830474", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830473, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73691", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, for what purposes their Department has used artificial intelligence in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 2, "answeringBodyName": "Scotland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Scotland Office: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830473", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830472, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73690", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, for what purposes their Department has used artificial intelligence in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 21, "answeringBodyName": "Northern Ireland Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Northern Ireland Office: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830472", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830471, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73689", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, for what purposes their Department has used artificial intelligence in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 217, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Culture, Media and Sport: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830471", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830470, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73688", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what purposes their Department has used artificial intelligence in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 13, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830470", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830469, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73687", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what purposes their Department has used artificial intelligence in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 27, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Transport", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Transport: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830469", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830468, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73686", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology, for what purposes their Department has used artificial intelligence in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 216, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Science, Innovation and Technology: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830468", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830467, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73685", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, for what purposes their Department has used artificial intelligence in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Business and Trade: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830467", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830466, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73684", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what purposes their Department has used artificial intelligence in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 29, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Work and Pensions", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Work and Pensions: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830466", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830465, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73683", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, for what purposes their Department has used artificial intelligence in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830465", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830464, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73682", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what purposes their Department has used artificial intelligence in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department for Education: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830464", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830463, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73681", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what purposes their Department has used artificial intelligence in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Department of Health and Social Care: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830463", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830462, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73680", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what purposes their Department has used artificial intelligence in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 7, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830462", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830461, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73679", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what purposes their Department has used artificial intelligence in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 54, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Justice", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Justice: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830461", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830460, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73678", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what purposes their Department has used artificial intelligence in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Ministry of Defence: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830460", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830459, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73677", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what purposes their Department has used artificial intelligence in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Home Office: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830459", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830458, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73676", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, for what purposes their Department has used artificial intelligence in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830458", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830457, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73675", "questionText": "To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what purposes their Department has used artificial intelligence in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 14, "answeringBodyName": "Treasury", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Treasury: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830457", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830456, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73674", "questionText": "To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what purposes their Department has used artificial intelligence in the last year.", "answeringBodyId": 53, "answeringBodyName": "Cabinet Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cabinet Office: Artificial Intelligence", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830456", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830455, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73673", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Energy Security and Net Zero, what components of wind turbines are (a) supplied and (b) manufactured in the UK.", "answeringBodyId": 215, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Energy Security and Net Zero", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Wind Power: Components", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830455", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830454, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73672", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what (a) diplomatic and (b) consular support his Department has given to Craig and Lindsay Foreman in the last three months.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Craig and Lindsay Foreman", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830454", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830453, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73671", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to support Craig and Lindsay Foreman in Iran.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Craig and Lindsay Foreman", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830453", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830452, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73670", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding has been allocated to local authorities to support (a) primary and (b) secondary school pupils who have English as a second language in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pupils: English Language", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830452", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830451, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73669", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions she has had with (a) teachers and (b) head teachers on teaching pupils who have English as a second language.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pupils: English Language", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830451", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830450, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73668", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an estimate of the total cost of support provided to pupils with English as an additional language in (a) primary and (b) secondary education in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pupils: English Language", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830450", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830449, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73667", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an estimate of the total cost of (a) translations and (b) interpretation services in (i) primary and (ii) secondary schools in each of the last three years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Schools: Interpreters and Translation Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830449", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830448, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73666", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what data her Department holds on the proportion of (a) primary and (b) secondary school pupils who do not speak English as their first language who arrived in the UK in each of the last five years.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pupils: English Language", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830448", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830447, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-02T00:00:00", "uin": "73665", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what data her Department holds on the number of (a) primary and (b) secondary school pupils who have English as a second language.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Pupils: English Language", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830447", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830446, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73664", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with NHS England on the feasibility of rolling out a national prostate cancer screening\u00a0initiative.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prostate Cancer: Screening", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830446", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830445, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73663", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of introducing a universal screening programme for prostate cancer on long-term NHS costs.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prostate Cancer: Screening", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830445", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830444, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73662", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to (a) raise awareness of prostate cancer symptoms and (b) encourage men to come forward for testing.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prostate Cancer: Health Education and Screening", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830444", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830443, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73661", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of disparities in access to prostate cancer testing among different socioeconomic groups.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prostate Cancer: Screening", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830443", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830442, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73660", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to ensure that men in areas with higher incidence rates of prostate cancer have targeted access to early screening.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prostate Cancer: Screening", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830442", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830441, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73659", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing a universal prostate cancer screening programme.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prostate Cancer: Screening", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830441", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830440, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73658", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve access to prostate cancer screening services.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prostate Cancer: Screening", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830440", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830439, "askingMemberId": 4743, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73657", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with (a) NICE and (b) NHS England on the (i) availability of and (ii) access to new treatments for patients with secondary breast cancer.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Breast Cancer: Medical Treatments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830439", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830438, "askingMemberId": 5339, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73656", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2025 to Question 64681 on Prostate Cancer: Hormone Treatments, for what reason recurrent headroom in revenue budgets is considered a barrier to implementing the abi", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Prostate Cancer: Hormone Treatments", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830438", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830437, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73655", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many confirmed cases of cholera there have been in the UK in the last 10 years.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Cholera", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830437", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830436, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73654", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what funding he is providing for defence innovation partnerships with (a) universities and (b) SMEs.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Innovation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830436", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830435, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73653", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy that all major trauma hospitals to have access to 24-hour helipad facilities.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Air Ambulance Services", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830435", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830434, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73652", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to consult with stakeholders before implementing changes to the (a) role and (b) title of Physician Associates.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Physician Assistants", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830434", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830433, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73651", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to implement the recommendations of the Independent review of the physician associate and anaesthesia associate roles, published on 16 July 2025.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Physician and Anaesthesia Associate Professions Independent Review", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830433", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830432, "askingMemberId": 5326, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73650", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an estimate of the potential impact of his proposed reforms to the Physician Associate role on the number of redundancies of Physician Associates.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Physician Assistants: Redundancy", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830432", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830431, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73649", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs, what assessment he has made of the humanitarian situation in Nigeria.", "answeringBodyId": 208, "answeringBodyName": "Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Nigeria: Humanitarian Situation", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830431", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830430, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73648", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the annual cost of fraud to the economy; and what assessment she has made of the potential impact of that cost on departmental funding decisions.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fraud", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830430", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830429, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73647", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to improve the effectiveness of fraud (a) prevention and (b) detection by public sector bodies.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Fraud: Public Sector", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830429", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830428, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73646", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Business and Trade, what resources he is providing to Companies House to (a) detect and (b) prevent the use of fraudulent corporate structures for criminal activity.", "answeringBodyId": 214, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Business and Trade", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Companies House", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830428", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830427, "askingMemberId": 4131, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73645", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to increase (a) funding and (b) staffing for public agencies responsible for investigating (i) fraud and (ii) economic crime.", "answeringBodyId": 1, "answeringBodyName": "Home Office", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Economic Crime", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830427", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830426, "askingMemberId": 5089, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73644", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential impact of the introduction of CBAM in January 2027 on defence procurement.", "answeringBodyId": 11, "answeringBodyName": "Ministry of Defence", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Defence: Procurement", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830426", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830425, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73643", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve access to urgent care services in areas where there is no A&E department within 10 miles.", "answeringBodyId": 17, "answeringBodyName": "Department of Health and Social Care", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Urgent Treatment Centres", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830425", "method": "GET"}]}, {"value": {"id": 1830424, "askingMemberId": 4844, "askingMember": null, "house": "Commons", "memberHasInterest": false, "dateTabled": "2025-09-01T00:00:00", "dateForAnswer": "2025-09-03T00:00:00", "uin": "73642", "questionText": "To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential impact of teacher recruitment and retention incentives on teacher recruitment and retention in areas of high deprivation in the (a) North East and (b) England.", "answeringBodyId": 60, "answeringBodyName": "Department for Education", "isWithdrawn": false, "isNamedDay": false, "groupedQuestions": [], "answerIsHolding": null, "answerIsCorrection": null, "answeringMemberId": null, "answeringMember": null, "correctingMemberId": null, "correctingMember": null, "dateAnswered": null, "answerText": null, "originalAnswerText": "", "comparableAnswerText": "", "dateAnswerCorrected": null, "dateHoldingAnswer": null, "attachmentCount": 0, "heading": "Teachers: Labour Turnover", "attachments": [], "groupedQuestionsDates": []}, "links": [{"rel": "self", "href": "/Questions/1830424", "method": "GET"}]}]